Coming up
What's got Sal all wound up?
What the hell is going on?!
Why is Joe oversharing?
I have a wife and bichon frise
who spend money like it's coming out of my metaphorical wiener.
And which joker can't escape tonight's punishment?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
We are at Sam Ash giving music lessons to students.
Aside from the fact that we have no musical ability
we won't know what instrument we're teaching until they walk in.
And to make things worse
we've recorded a secret song for each other.
They’ll be forced to play during the lesson.
The goal is to get your student to sign up for another lesson.
If you can't get them to sign up, you lose.
It's the jokers in a double down challenge.
How are you? You're here for your guitar lesson.
Electric guitar.
Have you done, like, any chords? You do that?
OK, so...
Joe, from this point forward, just refer to the guitar like it's a piano.
So you've never played piano before.
You want to make sure you don't touch any of the black keys in the middle.
The piano -- those ebonies and ivories. You never heard that before?
Yeah, but this is a guitar.
Oh, you're here for guitar.
What?
I've been teaching you piano on the guitar.
That makes more sense, yeah.
Hey, buddy, hit play on the boom box over there.
In this boom box here, I have a copy of my hit song.
I'd like you to hear it real quick
and you can just give me some honest feedback on it.
♪ death, destruction, diarrhea
♪ north and south Korea
♪ poo-poo
♪ murder
♪ death and constipation
♪ all the western nations
♪ bathroom time frustration
So, let's get back to our lesson.
Did you want to sign up for a follow-up class, or...?
It's OK.
It's OK? Yeah.
Well, my new single's coming out.
It's called "thumbs down".
Hey, what's up? How you doing? What's your name?
Hey, Joe, what's going on?
Drums!
"I'm actually in a band right now."
I'm in a band right now.
Buddy, we got a song for you to play.
Before we start, I got to play a song.
♪ I'm a sensitive guy
♪ with too much pride
♪ who loves a good cry
♪ just 'cause I'm a guy
♪ doesn't mean I don't cry
♪ I'll cry in front of you
♪ I'll cry on the moon
♪ cows say moo
♪ I cry with my shoes
♪ ah-choo
♪ god bless you
♪ let's cry
♪ I'm delicate.
"So, let me show you how to play,"
and just use your whole arms and go up and down, Sal
Let me show you how to play
—This guy's doing great on drums.  —Sure is.
Sal, just slam that cymbal.
Sal, have a cymbal face-off with this guy.
Just keep smacking it and looking him right in the eye.
Stare at him. Stare at him.
It's a standoff.
Wind it up. Wind it up.
Sal wins!
Would you think that you'd be interested to sign up for further lessons?
He got him!
This guy's serious about his ukulele.
Oh, my god.
—The ukulele.  —The old uke.
"Well, here's a fun fact about the ukulele."
Well, here's a fun fact about the ukulele.
"I’m lonely."
I'm lonely.
"So, let's see -- how's your rhythm?"
Let's check your rhythm first.
Put your ukuleles down.
Let's...put our ukuleles down.
"Now let's just clap to the rhythm."
And just -- just clap to the rhythm with me.
Clap as girly as you can.
1, 2, 1, 2.
1, 2, 3! 1, 2, 3!
OK, you're doing great.
Let's listen to your demo, buddy.
This is my demo.
♪ music is everywhere around you
♪ just tiny cigarettes in a suit
♪ football, porno, duck sauce, and popcorn
♪ I was born with both set of genitalia.
♪ help me.
"Help me."
I wrote that song.
Do you think, based on how this is going,
do you think you'd like to sign up for another ukulele lesson with me?
会
Here she comes.
Oh, no! Oh
The old stand-up bass!
Let me, uh...get my stand-up bass.
He doesn't even know how to take it off the stand!
Have you ever played the stand-up bass before?
Um...it's like a big violin.
"Have you ever played the violin before?"
Have you ever played the violin before?
A violin is like a small stand-up bass.
Like a guitar, you go the opposite ways, right?
And you can hear the different sounds as you go down.
"I promised myself I’d never fall for a student again..."
I promised myself that I would never fall for a student again.
"Then you walked in"
Like a guitar, you go the opposite ways, right?
And you can hear the different sounds as you go down.
"I promised myself I’d never fall for a student again..."
I promised myself that I would never fall for a student again.
"Then you walked in"
And then you walked in.
And here we are.
"I might be playing the strings..."
I might be playing the strings...
"...but you... are pulling the strings of my heart."
...but you... are pulling the strings of my heart.
Why don't we show her your demo?
I actually have a demo —
Me playing the stand-up bass.
So you can hear it.
♪ doo-be doo bop, dee ba
♪ ao-o-ga
♪ boo-ba-de da
♪ scooby-doo-gop doo
♪ doo-be doo bop, wee da
♪ ao-o-ga
♪ doo-ba-da da
♪ doo-ba-da geh
♪ di di
You heard all the quality stand-up bass in there, right?
Yeah, so, what do you say?
You want to sign up for another class?
Don't do it.
All right!
—how?!  —we made it too fun!
Joe couldn't hit the right note, so he's on the loser board.
Hey, hey! Focus up, America!
Today, one of us will be the moderator in a focus group...
ad the other will be participating in that same group.
Now, the participant must read all the answers on his survey.
The thing is, his completely embarrassing answers have been written by the moderator.
If you can't read every answer, in its entirety, you lose.
Shh. Q's really focused.
It's Murr vs Joe and Q vs Sal in a double showdown.
Murr, the dress code today was Steven Seagal, so good job.
Hi, everyone. Welcome to Focus Suites.
Joe has got to answer all the questions that Murray wrote for him
as his own and own those answers.
So, Murr, if Joe answers all those questions, you lose.
OK. So, first, Michelle, where do you get your news primarily from?
Mostly from social networks.
Social networking. So online. OK.
And how would you, Erica?
Yeah, I said Twitter but also social media in general.
OK, and, Joe, where do you get your news from?
Here we go.
I think I ate too much cheese this morning.
That's what you wrote as the answer?
Yeah. Uh, re-reading this, I guess, uh... I misunderstood.
OK.
How did you get here today?
—Michelle?  —Train.
—You took the subway?  —Mm-hmm.
—And Alexis.  —Subway.
Subway. And, Joe, same question.
Oh. I took this a little bit more.
This is all open interpretation,
but I said, "subway,"
But originally, I came here from my mom's Tallahassee
A.k.a. Her rubber ducky...
...a.k.a. Her strawberry smoothie.
Murr's getting his ass handed to him.
Does price greatly influence your choice of technology purchases?
Howie, how about you?
Yeah, for a student, I would say it does. It does, for sure.
And, Joe, how about you?
I wrote, uh...
I have a wife and bichon frise
who spend money like it's coming out of my wiener.
Murray, you got to get Joe here, man.
He's coming out swinging.
I'm sorry. What is a bichon frise?
It's a bichon frise. It's a little puppy.
How does the bichon frise spend your money?
Oh, the bichon frise eats a specialty diet
via the wife spending the money like it's coming out of my metaphorical wiener.
Joe really took ownership of that one.
I feel like there was some truth there.
OK. You better pull out a big gun, Murr
because he has got you on the ropes.
Final question -- Joe, on a lazy Sunday afternoon
what is your preferred activity?
I dutch oven my cats, mostly.
No, I dutch oven my cats 'cause that's what I said.
Joey!
Looks like we've gotten through every question.
Here we go.
Q is in the driver's seat.
Alright, Sal. Good luck, buddy.
So, Q has written all of Sal’s answers.
Sal will be reading what Q makes him say.
OK. We have Steven, right? Courtney, uh, Al...
He called him Al!
Sal. Sal.
Sal. OK, cool. Sorry.
No problem.
And here we go.
OK. We'll just start.
Dwayne, do you have a nickname?
—No.  —No, no nickname.
Uh, OK, Al. Do you have a nickname?
Sal. Um...bologna cheeks.
Where did you get the nickname "bologna cheeks"?
Friends gave it to me.
It's relatively new.
"It’s relatively new"!
Stuck, huh?
It better not stick.
You're coming out hot right away, Q.
Uh, OK. Let me ask you another one.
Please, thinking about smartphones, what comes to mind?
—Courtney?  —apps, taking pictures.
Perfect.
That was an excellent answer.
But you know who I think is gonna have a better answer?
—Al?  —Al's.
OK, uh... Al, think about smartphones, what comes to mind?
The time that I... accidentally sent a naked selfie to my sister...
...and then she sent one back, so...
Great answer!
"And she sent one back"?!
Wait a second.
She sent back a naked -- a naked picture of herself?
He's turning the screws!
We've all been there.
No.
Next question.
Steven, you want to start with it? What do you do for fun?
I play basketball in my local community center.
Ok, Al?
It's Sal.
I thought I said "Sal" and you said it's "Al."
No, it's -- it's been Sal since I’ve been born.
And what do you do for fun?
Uh, I love to paint.
—Paint?  —Mm-hmm.
What do you paint?
There's more to that answer.
What I wrote here was...
I use acrylic paint... and a mirror between my legs.
It's a -- its art, man.
—OK, I'm just not understanding how it works.  —It's art.
It's subjective.
Q is gloating!
Q's got something up his sleeve.
What are you painting?
I do whatever it takes to, uh...make art.
Uh, very unclear on what's -- what it means.
Ha! You got to answer, buddy.
I guess I -- I don't know. Maybe I... taint paint.
All right, well, follow-up question for you, then?
And I promise it'll be the last one.
It all comes down to this.
On a lazy afternoon, what's your preferred activity?
Well, it depends.
If there is a girs...
He's pointing the guns at him!
If there's a girl with me...
Oh! It's a Mexican standoff!
Sal's got a gun! A Mexican standoff!
...I like to be, uh... lazy all over her.
Let me know if you don't get it.
Oh! He does it!
We're all done here.
Oh, too bad, Q.
Even after all of that, Joe remains tonight's big loser.
Joe! Aren't punishments magical?
Super-magical.
Tonight, at the Borgata Hotel Casino & Spa
the great nozini is gonna dazzle a packed house with a night of magic and illusion.
We've billed you as a world-famous escape artist.
You got to go in there and thrill the audience.
Good punishment, boys.
This is a packed crowd.
We're at the Borgata.
They don't put up half-assed shows.
They're gonna expect the most amazing magic ever.
Ladies and gentlemen
The time has come to lay your eyes upon the greatest escape artist of our time.
Joe Gatto!
Good evening, and welcome to a night of magic and illusion.
I am an escape artist, and that's what I’ll be doing.
I'll be escaping... before your very eyes.
I hope you are ready to be amazed.
So, let's get on with the escaping.
A straightjacket will be put on me.
How do you like that, bud?
You're gonna have to get out of a straightjacket.
Straightjackets are known for being hard to get out of -- some would say impossible.
To that, I say... wait and see.
I will now escape from this straightjacket.
But that's not all.
I will be bound in steel chains and rope around my ankles.
Thank you, ladies.
So, now I have a straightjacket, steel chains, and rope around my legs.
And I will now escape before your very eyes.
Wait. There's more.
What? What the...?
Not before I’m... lowered into... this...chamber of water.
I love you guys.
Lowered into the chamber of water to up the ante.
Hey, Joe! [bleep] you!
I'm pretty sure this is how many escape artists die.
I will now escape from this chamber of water.
Look at his face!
Hey, Joe, how do you feel? Great?
Oh, that's cold.
Oh, what's going through his mind right now?
I will now escape.
Any moment now.
Any moment now!
Oh, oh, wait!
What?
Nope.
This is taking a bit longer than I expected.
They really did a number with this straightjacket.
These chains are a [bleep].
Well, at this point, this is useless. I'm sorry.
He's apologizing!
—Joe thought that being embarrassed by not escaping would be the punishment.  —No.
—No.  —That wasn't his punishment. This part is the punishment.
There's just silence.
He's just staring at them like he's a zoo animal.
There's people leaving?
Have a good day, ma'am.
People are booing him!
I appreciate your faith in me, folks.
No, I can't.
Joe, you got to pee, buddy?
I just did.
The stage lights are off!
Guys, let's put him out of his misery.