Coming up, why does Sal want to play dress-up?
I would love to see what you look like in a burka.
Has Q found his soul mate?
He said yes!
And what has tonight's big loser turning story time into scary time?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Tonight we're at the 7-in-heaven at the beautiful Long Beach Hotel.
And we're here for one reason -- to embarrass ourselves in front of singles.
While mingling with the lovely people of Long Beach
We're gonna have to do and say whatever the other guys tell us to do.
And if you refuse anything you're told, you'll lose and you die alone.
Let's get it, boys.
What?
This is actually a jumpin' event.
All right, boys.
Here you go, buddy. You're gonna find your soul mate.
Intimidating, to say the least.
On the prowl, Sal Vulcano. Haven't seen this since college.
Be gentle with me.
I'll call you tomorrow, I promise.
How you doing, bud?
Cheers.
Sal.
Nice to meet you, Larry. What's going on, man?
Larry.
"My friend Joe was looking for you."
My friend was looking for you before.
Yeah, the ticket line, he was looking for you at the supermarket.
He was looking for you at the shoe store.
He couldn't find you anywhere.
Get in there, Larry.
How you doing?
What's going on?
To mingle.
Sal, get really overemotional with everything.
You big crybaby.
Wednesday's -- Wednesday's my favorite day.
It's, like, people call it hump day like it's a bad thing.
He's getting emotional about Wednesdays.
But I just think, like, it's like the best day
Everybody loves Friday, Saturday, and Sunday.
Everybody has feelings about Monday.
But people forget about Wednesday.
Are you getting sentimental on me?
I just -- I just think Wednesday's the tops.
Oh, my god. You're crying over Wednesday. That's crazy.
I must be extra emotional.
Start crying about it. Say no and start crying.
I -- I actually haven't...
I am suffering out here.
Oh, my god. This is tough.
I should probably be in therapy. I got, like, voices in my head.
No, yeah, that's great.
That's the nicest woman on Long Island!
Hey, how are you?
Jennifer.
How's everything?
Good, good.
"Anyone ever tell you you're the splitting image of Vanessa Williams?"
Anyone ever tell you you're the splitting image of Vanessa Williams?
No, but just the features.
"Man, I'd love to see what you look like in a burka."
Man, I would love to see what you look like in a burka.
"Something you should know about me right off the top."
There's something you should know about me right off the top.
"I only do kisses till marriage."
I only do kisses until marriage.
"The vagina."
Uh... The -- the vagina.
Until marriage.
I mean, and I am strict with that.
There he is.
Look at this handsome son of a bitch.
Look at him. He's partying the sea of singles.
I need a drink.
Good, good. How are you?
While you're talking to this lady, keep checking yourself to see if you have b.o.
What was your name?
Irene!
I'm just checking if I put enough deodorant on, you know.
Q, twirl your hair.
Look at her face!
What's up?
This guy's [bleep] blocking you!
What?! He got boxed out!
It's prison rules out there!
Thanks for [bleep] blocking me, bro.
Hi, my name's Brian.
"You know you don't need to refrigerate mayo, right?"
You know you don't need to refrigerate mayo? Did you know that?
Yeah.
Q, just keep talking about mayo, bud.
We used to put mayo on everything, not just sandwiches.
We used to put mayo on, like, shrimp.
We used to put mayo on, like, pizza.
Do you have any mayo for that, actually?
Do you have any mayo you could throw on that?
Yeah, if you could grab some mayo, that would be great. Thank you.
She's doing "help me" eyes.
What do you do?
"Bor-ring!"
So, if I ran over my friends with a car...
...you could insure that?
I'm James, nice to meet you, Linda.
Pleasure.
Where you from?
Merrick? Oh, sure.
I used to date a girl who lived in Merrick.
Murr, you waxing your eyebrows?
'Cause that's what it looks like from here, buddy.
Two perfectly-shaped little pencil eyebrows.
What about the beard?
You look like George Michael.
I'm sorry. I'm thrown off my game right now.
Salud.
I think he played it perfect.
We have something flying in to help you out a little bit.
What are you talking about?
See those business cards?
Put them in your pocket.
Don't look at them.
Put them in your pocket. Do not look.
Go introduce yourself to people, hand them the card, and live with it, my friend.
See those business cards?
Yeah.
Don't look at them.
Go introduce yourself to people, hand them the card, and live with it, my friend.
Cheers. Nice to meet you.
Oh, here we go!
I'll give you my card.
My name's James Murray. I'm a child-pageant coach.
What I do is I make purses for cats.
My name's James Murray. I'm a state executioner.
My name is James Murray. I'm a douche manufacturer.
Douches?
是的NYeah.
My name's James Murray, defense attorney.
I'll give you the D.
I'm single and ready to mingle, boys.
No, you are not single!
Put that wedding ring back on!
Yes, yes! Yes, you scumbag!
There you go.
Tap the glass with your finger.
You can see in his face. He's actually tense about it.
She noticed. She just noticed.
Go up to this woman and say, "We've got to make this quick. My wife thinks I'm at the movies."
Hi, sorry. I got to make this quick. My wife thinks I'm at the movies.
Uh...just, first impression, yes or no?
Um...you make a nice first impression, but I'm...
No, you're not. OK, I appreciate it. Thank you.
I'll just keep circulating.
How you doing? Are you from out here, Edith, or no?
Amityville.
Oh, OK. I'm Staten Island.
You gonna call him?
I'm gonna call him.
If I need a passport...
It's not gonna work out.
Joe, slowly mention that you're married.
I'm sorry. It's just my wife.
That was your wife?
What? Yeah.
You were supposed to go to the pharmacy to get her some medicine.
Come on, man!
I was supposed to go to the pharmacy to get her some medicine.
She keeps calling me. Well, she's real sick, so...
But, you know, I'm at this thing.
I'm calling again.
It's like boys' night out by myself, but she --
I'm sorry. Let me answer that. Just one second.
Hi, honey.
Honey, where are you?
I'm just at this singles event, speaking to Edith.
She just leaves. She's walking away!
How's the emphysema?
Later, scumbag.
You guys are heartless.
Here we go.
It's the blonde from earlier!
Oh, she's coming over.
Oh, no, no. She thinks that I'm at the movies.
Oh.
Keep referring to your glass eye.
Oh, this glass eye is killing me.
These lights are... They're streaming.
I feel like a deer on the throughway.
Look at his glass eye!
You keep it in a little jar by your bed?
A mason jar, yeah. It came from my in-laws.
They gave me one for the wedding.
Keep missing the glass.
It does kill you. The glass eye just gets you every time.
My glass eye. My wife is home sick with emphysema.
I'm a train wreck, right.
So, what are you, a Libra?
Q is single but couldn't mingle, so he's up on the loser board.
Today, we're on the streets trying to borrow people's cellphones to make a call.
But we don't know who we're calling, why we're calling them, or what happened to our phones.
The other guys will be giving us that information on these cue cards.
If you can't get the person to lend you their phone, you lose.
That's it! Boom!
Sal, before we begin, just to check the odds of you succeeding here
Would you ever let a stranger borrow your phone on the street?
They would have to be...
Bleeding.
...bleeding, but then I wouldn't want to do it, either, so...
My man, I got to make a quick call.
I got to call...
a white guy named Ja'Crispy.
You know what I'm saying?
My white friend. His name's Ja'Crispy, though. His parents have a great sense of humor.
I got to tell him... It's cuddle o'clock.
I know what you're thinking -- why can't I use my phone?
I wouldn't be asking, but...
Very simple. My phone converted to Judaism.
Can I use your phone, man?
I mean, you've been so patient with me.
My man, I got to make a quick call.
I wouldn't be asking, but...
I got to call... a white guy named Ja'Crispy.
You know what I'm saying?
Can I use you phone, man?
I named my son Ja'Crispy -- is that a lifetime of fun or a lifetime of agony?
That's a mistake.
Why?
Nah.
What if I changed my name to Ja'Crispy?
Wouldn't that make your life better?
Ja'Crispy Vulcano?
I do you like.
How about you just go, OK? Enough with the Ja'Crispy.
Call me Ja'Crispy and I'll go.
Go ahead, Ja'Crispy.
Hey, bud. I got to make a quick call.
It's a funny story. I got to call...
I'm not kidding. I need to call batman.
Batman?
Yeah. I'm not even kidding.
Thank you.
Oh, you got a cellphone.
Hey, bud, I was wondering
can I borrow the cellphone real quick? I got to make a phone call.
I got to call a pancake.
I got to make a quick call to a pancake.
No? Yeah, that's all it would take, really.
I think that's fine. Because who calls a [bleep] pancake?
Oh, hi, kids. Sorry about that.
Excuse me, bud. I was wondering -- I got to make a phone call
So could you help me out real quick?
I was just -- I have to call... a nun who loves guacamole.
I got to tell her...
Well, she's not answering my hate mail, 'cause...
She hates you?
No, she's a nun, she can't hate me.
She's just not answering my hate mail. I hate her.
I'm -- I'm getting late for somewhere.
Oh, but can I just borrow it? I can walk with --
No, no, no, no, no!
Thank you, bud. Let's call her. Thank you. I appreciate it.
It's a 212 number, so it's local.
It's 1-212-386 niner-eight.
You just made this number up!
No, no. Hit call. Just hit call. There you go.
Thank you, boss.
"You just made it up!"
Hey, sister Margaret Mary, answer my hate mail.
Excuse me, sir, could I ask you for a favor?
I have to call my personal trainer real quick.
Because, well, I have to tell him, quite frankly...
Jaden Smith said "yes".
Jaden Smith looked at me and said "yes"!
And I left my phone in the Swiss diplomat's toilet.
Don't ask how it got there.
Can I use your phone just to call my personal trainer? I can?
No way! Son of a...
Hello?
Gregorio!
Put down those weights, you so-and-so!
Jaden Smith said "yes".
All right, jerk. We got it.
All right, cool. I'll talk to you later.
I was wondering if I could get a favor from you guys?
You guys look like you might be able to help.
I have to call someone.
I have to call my coroner.
I know this sounds a little weird.
I have to tell him that I'm...
Oh, god, Sal.
You got to say it, Q.
I have to tell him he did a good job on my grandmother.
Have a good day, guys.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry to bother you guys. Sorry.
Starting a racist cover band?
Excuse me, guys. I'm at a loss, here. I was supposed to meet somebody.
And I was supposed to call them, but my phone is gone.
I was supposed to call your mother.
And the reason why is I was going to tell her that, uh...
that she's got to check the ransom.
I was gonna call your mom about the ransom, and, uh...
"You're about to be taken."
...'cause you're about to be taken.
"I have a very specific set of skills."
I have a very specific set of skills.
There's no reason to back away. I'm not the one taking you.
I'm gonna be the one that recovers you.
You gonna pass on the phone call? OK. No problem.
They're running!
That's not the first time a woman's run from Murray.
I got a question for you.
Funny, crazy thing -- I'm trying to -- I have to make a phone call, right?
I'm trying to call Aerosmith.
You know them, right? I was try to call Aerosmith
and I got to call them quick because I...
I need to curse them out.
The problem is, I left my phone...
caught between the mo--
My phone...
You know where I left my phone?
Let me tell you...
Just take it, you idiot!
Do you mind if I call them?
I'm gonna call -- OK. Thank you, man. You are a gentleman.
Uh, yes, Mr. Tyler?
Yeah [bleep] you, Tyler.
Q couldn't dial up a win, making him tonight's big loser.
Once upon a time, Q lost.
Today, we're at the Brooklyn Children's Museum, and it's story time.
Every week, parents bring their kids to hear a children's author read their latest work.
Today, buddy, you're gonna be reading your children's book
based on your very own life, that we all wrote.
I have a feeling I won't be living happily ever after.
No, definitely not.
The end, bitch.
These mommies are very excited to spend some quality time with their kids.
You know, to meet a new author.
Then comes in our friend in the velour jacket.
Hi, everybody.
Hi!
How are you, guys?
I'm Brian Quinn, and I have my book called...
"The remarkable misadventures of Q the dung beetle"
It's based on my actual life, which I find is always the best inspiration.
Meet Q the dung beetle!
He loves super heroes and tacos.
Q was the silliest dung beetle in all the land.
"I may be a beetle, but I'm a silly goose."
Yeah, he's a silly goose.
They love it.
But Q was often too silly for his own good.
Rumblings of a problem.
"The remarkable misadventures of Q the dung beetle"
It's based on my actual life.
Q was often too silly for his own good.
During an important work meeting, he knocked over his glass of water.
"Tidal wave!" He guffawed.
"This is no laughing matter," said Q's boss, Mr. Grasshopper.
"The company's hemorrhaging money."
Look at this little girl. She knows something's up.
"Hey, Mr. Grasshopper, don't bug out!' Q squelched.
"Wipe that [bleep] damn smirk off your face," said Mr. Grasshopper.
"Security, please escort Q the dung beetle out of the building.
Good luck living with yourself."
Oh, my god.
Things also began spiraling out of control at home.
They're about to learn about two harsh words -- domestic dispute.
"You're projecting your insecurities onto me," said Q's wife.
She swiped up a vase and lunged into the sheetrock.
Shattered ceramic littered the carpet.
"I'm leaving you, Q the dung beetle."
Oh, no. Now [bleep] really hitting the fan.
Q peered over to find the children cowering at what they had witnessed.
"Your mother's a gold dunger."
All right, guys, it's gonna get better.
No, it's not!
How much?
Explain that.
What's going on here is he's -- he's -- he is alone.
There's, like, uncomfortable laughter.
Sometimes, you know... even dung beetles need companions.
He is sweating.
Q ate microwave dinner over the kitchen sink.
Look at the bloodshot eyes.
Drinking beer!
Drinking beer? Yeah.
The red eyes are from drinking beer. You're very astute.
Look at the parents!
"Now, what does every children's story have?"
Now, what does every children's story have?
A happy ending! That's right!
So what did you learn from the book?
Did anybody learn any lessons from the book?
Yes?
That's right.
Thank you so much, everybody.
Yeah! Q the children's author!
That's a happy ending for us.