What's got Joe and Murr screeching for joy?
Why is Murr up in arms over a penguin?
I've had it with you!
And what's got tonight's big loser running scared?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Today we are in the park, giving each other embarrassing tasks
using the official "Impractical Jokers" voice modulator.
So, our voices that normally sound like this...
Now sound like this.
But here's the catch -- you have to try and guess
whose disguised voice gave you the command.
If you guess incorrectly, you have to perform the task.
But if you guess correctly, that person has to come out and do it themself.
And as always, if you can't do what you're told, you lose.
Let's do this, Brutus.
—You can hear me, buddy?  —Yes.
—Can you tell who this is?  —No clue.
The ransom's set at $1 million.
Give me back my son!
You're about to be taken.
Give me some jabba the hutt.
—I like your scarf.  —Oh, Joe.
Yeah, that's right.
—My feet hurt.  —Sal. How are you, buddy?
—I hate myself.  —Wait, how did I get on the mic?
Here's the issue here, OK?
You want to give him something hard to do.
But...if it's too hard and he guesses you, you have to do it.
That's right. Yeah.
You might screw yourself.
OK, you ready, buddy?
Burp someone.
Burp someone?
Well, let me think about this.
Murray doesn't like that sort of humor.
Sal can burp really well, so burping might be on his mind.
Uh...I'm gonna go with Sal.
Have fun burping someone, buddy.
That was Joe.
Since he didn't guess it, you escaped it.
Oh, what's going on, bro? How are you?
You're looking a little gassy. Come on.
Get it out. Get it out. Get it out.
Burp it out. Burp it out.
Come on. Burp it out.
You pat me. I pat you. We'll both burp at the same time.
Ready? One, two, three.
He got it!
There you go, bud.
I'm better now, buddy. Thank you.
All right, boys.
Not bad, buddy, but the only way you come back in is if you guess one right.
Right. You got to guess who said it.
All right. Sure. Give me the next one.
Put someone's fingers in your mouth.
Murray.
No way!
Murray, 'cause only Murray would tell us to do something stupid like that.
You're right.
No! No!
Get out there and get people's fingers in your mouth.
Can you do me a favor?
I'm testing out a new magic trick.
Can I test it on you real quick? It takes 10 seconds.
I'm going to make your fingers disappear.
OK, so, what I need you to do is this.
It's an illusion, OK? Like, as narrow as you can get.
OK, now, here's how it works.
You just take this, do this.
And the trick is very simple. You go...
Ta-da
He did it.
Holy [bleep]
Wow! That's great.
How's victory taste, buddy?
Tastes like a subway.
Now you're up.
Oh. All right. Give it to me.
Play air guitar and air drums in someone's personal space.
OK, this is interesting.
Sal doesn't like invading people's personal space,
But he does like showmanship.
You are a showman.
Well, Q is the video-game guy, and Q plays the air guitar and the air drums.
You play that air-guitar video game all the time?
Clearly, the answer is Sal.
Yeah! You're up.
Do it, idiot.
Not clever enough for the old Murr.
There you go.
I knew it. Get out there!
He looks crazy.
Oh, he's putting the guitar on!
Is she just trying to ignore the concert that's going on?
He did the Marty McFly right by her.
Ah! He's chasing her off.
Drum solo.
She's dancing! She's headbanging.
The best concert she has been invited to.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
—Well done, Sal.  —Sal, nicely tossed.
Guys, enough is enough now.
You can't stop until you guess who's saying it, buddy.
OK, OK.
This isn't over until someone loses.
Kiss this blonde on the lips.
This is Joe. This is Joe Gatto.
Go kiss that blond girl. Go kiss her.
She's beautiful.
I know she is. It's Joe. This is Joe Gatto.
That sounds like Q to me.
No, it doesn't!
He's putting mints in his mouth.
Now you have to go kiss her, show-off.
Hey, how are you?
I'm good.
Good. What's going on?
Uh, I'm just -- I was just hanging out in the park.
Nice to meet you.
Do you come around here often?
Uh... I go to school here.
—This is hard to watch.  —I would just kiss.
All right. Well, it was nice to meet you. Bye.
All right. Well, it was nice to meet you.
—This is hard to watch.  —I would just kiss.
Bye.
Ok.
We have a loser.
Game over.
Sal kisses his win goodbye.
Enough is enough. We quit.
Today Murr and Sal will be posing as employees at different locations.
But not for long 'cause we have to quit our jobs in front of a ton of people.
The reason that you're quitting will be given to you by the other guys.
The goal is to get the crowd to applaud for you,
No matter how ridiculous the reason.
If they can't rile up the crowd, they lose.
I am gonna quit so fantastically.
It's Murr versus Sal in a "joker versus joker" challenge.
Do you want the hanger or...?
Ah, another hard day at work.
You know what? You're better than this, man.
You want to get out and follow your dreams.
All right, Sal. It's time to get out.
Get everyone's attention and let them know why you're quitting.
Remember -- you have to get them to applaud.
Excuse me, ladies and gentlemen.
Could I have your attention, please?
Oh! It got quiet!
I just want to let you know that I am quitting...
Why are you quitting?
'Cause your father forced you into the field of discount retail.
...because it was my dad who pressured me into the field of discount retail.
—And you are breaking free to follow your dreams!  —Yes!
And I'm leaving to finally follow my own dreams, that's all I'm saying.
I just want to say that out loud.
What are these dreams? I can't wait to find out.
My dreams include but are not limited to
Following Jamiroquai around the world...
—Who's Jamiroquai?  —He's a singer.
—A beloved '90s pop icon.  —Oh.
...'cause I'm a huge fan.
He's got the hat. He's got "Virtual Insanity."
He's got the other hits.
Sal, is Jamiroquai your only dream? Dream bigger, buddy.
The other thing I'm gonna do --
And i've always wanted to do it -- is blog about fruit.
I think fruit is delicious and nutritious
And I want to get the word out.
Bananas, apples, oranges.
Don't even get me started on the plums.
You know what I'm talking about!
Why can't you work here and blog about fruit?
It's too much for one life.
Also, Chandra in textiles can be a real B when she wants to.
And i've had it up to here with that.
So, I just ask you to support me in my decision to follow my dreams.
For any of you who have been pressured by your parents into discount retail...
...to join me and stick up for what you believe in and follow your dreams.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
I'm quitting to follow Jamiroquai and blog about fruit!
He got it. He got it. All right, man.
Thank you. I don't know if you heard it. I quit.
Hi, everyone, how are you?
Come on down, guys.
Murr works here in the zoo but not for long
Sal quit his job. Now Murr's up.
My name is James. I'm a zookeeper.
What this crowd doesn't know
Is that Murray cannot take this job anymore
And he is about to have a breakdown.
And you've seen these guys already, right?
Anybody know how fast they can swim underwater?
You know what? I'm sorry. I can't do this.
You know, I'm sorry, guys. I...I can't do this. I quit...
It's because of all this penguin drama.
...because of all the penguin drama.
The rest is all you, buddy. Good luck.
I'll tell you -- it's hard working here.
I've been here for four years now working in this zoo
And the penguin drama is just really hard.
It's ridiculous.
I've had it with you!
Everything in the world is not black and white!
Save the drama for your penguin mama!
He expects to win the crowd over by berating cute little animals?
He's going the complete wrong direction.
This one pooped in my shoe on purpose last week.
I've had it, and I quit!
Who's had enough of the penguin drama? Who's with me?
No one?
No, little girl.
That's not the answer I was hoping for.
I'm standing here as a zookeeper
Saying, "Who's with me quitting today?" Who?!
It's people like you are the reason
that this penguin drama goes on and on and on.
I'm feeding them fish. You're feeding their egos!
He's now berating them.
The whole goal is to get them to cheer with him.
Come on. You're killing me.
My friend, you played that horribly wrong.
That didn't work at all.
Murr's not a good quiter, but he is a good loser.
Coming up, what's got tonight's big loser running for his life?
Today we are teaming up to drop some prehistoric knowledge,
Giving lectures as dinosaur experts.
It's team Indiana versus team Jurassic Park.
But here's the thing -- we don't know jack about dinosaurs
And our presentations have been made by the other team.
At the end, we'll ask the audience to raise their hands
If they'd like to take another class with us.
Whichever team gets the fewest hands raised is extinct.
Snakes! We hate snakes!
Why are you limping?
I mean, I got a walking stick. What do you want me to do?
You look like an eccentric billionaire who owns his own island.
Welcome to Staten Island.
Hey, guys, how are you?
Hi. Welcome.
Have a seat, please.
Thank you for joining.
We are here to give a little presentation on dinosaurs.
All right, let's get started, then.
So, "Dinosaurs: Ancient History and Cutting-edge Science."
We're gonna start at the beginning and build up from there.
"Evolutionary Chart."
Apparently, I can't even make it to human.
You'll get there one day.
We all have our downfalls.
Moving on.
"Wang... Wang length by dinosaur."
We travel around to all different zoos, museums
And we get questions
You know, like, "Dinosaurs were huge."
"How big were their wangs?"
The stegosaurus is just embarrassing.
Right. Big brain. Little wang.
We all went to high school.
We all had -- you know, you go out on a date, you going on first base.
First base is up top -- here.
Right, everything that's above.
Second base, we're looking at those.
The T-rex couldn't get to second because...
How you gonna get them ta-tas?
Excuse me.
Yes, dear.
Oh, my god. I feel very weird now.
So, that is our presentation today.
OK, now let me just ask how many -- by a show of hands --
Would take a follow-up class with us?
One, two.
Not even half.
We're going to cruise control on this one.
We spared no expense.
Let's do it, Indiana.
Two dr. Joneses right there.
Sorry if I'm out of breath, guys. I just ran from a boulder.
Hi, folks. How are you?
—Come on in.  —Come on in. Have a seat.
We're going to take you through a presentation --
Facts That You May or May Not Know About Dinosaurs.
Here we go.
"New dinosaur species are still being discovered today."
They estimate there may be as much as 1,000 more species still undiscovered.
Next slide.
Cute Dinosaur Jokes That I Wrote
This woman's falling asleep...
I dino-bored her to sleep.
She's sleeping.
Fascinating, right?
That was actually its mating ritual.
Find out where this is going. There.
Of course, we will show you the dance.
This is actually how these two idiots pick up girls in bars.
She just woke up.
She is up, now.
By show of hands, how many of you think you would take another class with us?
Three.
—OK.  —Alright.
Q and Sal got fossilized, making Sal tonight's big loser.
We're in the middle of a cornfield
And, Sal, for your punishment, all you have to do
Is get from one side of the cornfield to the other.
The only rules are you've got to hang on to that guide rope.
Guys, I tell you right now, if it's a haunted maze
[bleep] is gonna go down because I'm gonna punch someone.
I don't take haunts well.
Look out!
If there's one thing Sal hates more than germs and cats,
It's haunted houses, ghouls.
Getting scared is like his worst fear.
I'm telling you right now -- if there's monsters in there...
You're acting like a child.
Even if they're not real monsters and they just tickle you instead
I'm ticklish, too. I'll still punch if I'm getting tickled.
There's tickle monsters in the cornfield. Busted. We're busted.
Grab the  rope!
If someone comes at me -- this is expensive equipment?
Yes.
Hand on the rope! Hand on the rope and get walking!
If anybody comes out, I'm liable to punch you
And I know there's not such a thing as real monsters, so...
Oh my god!
If anybody comes out, I'm liable to punch you
And I know there's not such a thing as real monsters, so...
Laugh it up, Murray, you idiot.
If you're gonna jump out, be prepared for a fight.
We purposefully didn't put anything in the first twists and turns.
Does anybody look up -- what about the ticks in here?
Ticks in a cornfield?
Nah. No. They got bedbugs.
Aah! Oh, my god.
What do you scream at?
The [bleep] corn keeps hitting me in the head.
I'm so scaring now.
Oh... My... God!
There's a little girl in a dress staring at me.
Who's the girl in the dress staring at me?!
What girl in a dress?
There's a little girl in a dress staring at me.
She's not supposed to be there, buddy.
Well, she's there! Is she a ghost?!
You lied! It's a haunted maze!
Guys, guys, I'm not walking toward that little girl.
What are you talking about?!
Go! Follow the rope.
Holy [bleep]
No, I'm scared out of my mind!
Did you pass her yet?
No, I'm staring at her!
Don't stare at her. That gets her angry.
Guys, I'm not -- ohh! She's telling me to come to her!
You know what? Let's just get it out in the open.
You see, little girl, I will not hesitate to punch you!
I can't go near her.
Oh, my god. That's really weird.
You need to go find an adult.
I know I'm gonna look so stupid on this camera.
I get it. My face is gonna be like a big fishbowl right in the camera.
And I'm gonna run, and  everyone's gonna mock me.
A [bleep] air horn blew. I fell on my face.
Hey, Sal, you haven't seen any birds in there or anything, right?
No.
So, all right.
So, something's keeping those birds away, I guess.
All right, cool. Thanks.
What is it? It's a damn scarecrow!
Oh, that's why there's no birds.
It's gonna jump right on me.
Oh, man. I don't want to pass it. I don't want to pass it.
I am not walking past that thing.
This is where it goes down, man! I will take a swing at you!
Oh, this is the worst --
You [bleep] son of a bitch! You son of a bitch. You ass [bleep].
Oh, god. Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
What the [bleep] is that?!
That's not [bleep]
Enough!
It's not a Sal punishment without heaping piles of [bleep].
I'm sinking in! I'm sinking in the [bleep]!
This [bleep] is all over me.
Oh, god. I'm gonna throw up. I smell like [bleep].
What the [bleep] does that mean?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
That's it, bud.
There you go, pal.
You did it. You got to the end.
Now you just got to figure out your way out.
Guys, are you serious?
Yep.
That's it, bud. There you go, pal.
I guess I'll just have to run in one direction here.
Sal wants to run out of the cornfield.
I bet you we can find a way to make him run.