We just landed in the lone star state!
We're gonna be lassoing up trouble all over the wild, wild west
trying to humiliate each other.
And when it's all over, the loser's gonna be served up some Texas-style justice!
So saddle up, partner!
It's gonna be a showdown to remember!
This offensive stereotype is only missing one thing.
What's that?
Draw! Draw!
Texas draw! Texas draw!
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Howdy!
We're at texas ranch life in Chappell hill
a dude ranch where people come to learn real-deal cowboy skills.
And today, we're partnering up as ranch experts
to teach some city slickers the ropes.
Besides the fact that all we know about ranch is dressing
We've also prepared each others' lessons.
At the end of the lesson
we're gonna ask those folks if they learned anything of value.
Whoever gets the fewest hands raised loses.
I just saw a horse piss on That hay.
Oh [bleep]
Howdy, folks. How are you?
Oh, he said "howdy" for credibility right up top.
We'll take you through some of the basics of what's it like
living, working on a ranch.
Bump butts and yell, "Cowboys."
Cowboys!
Murr, OK, so, let's get a Volunteer.
OK. What we need is a volunteer.
Ah, there we go.
Murr, take 10 large steps Back.
1... 2...
3... 4... 5...
6... 7... 8...
9 -- my chaps are falling -- 10.
"I am going to lasso you."
I'm going to lasso you.
She's like, "What the hell?"
Murray has never picked up a lasso in his life.
This is the first time he's holding a lasso.
Now, keep your hands down. This won't hurt.
Moving along...
So, we're gonna show you how to use a bullwhip.
Murr, every time you do it, Go, "wha-pish!"
It's the change in direction that makes the classic sound of a whip.
Wha-pish!
You hear it?
It's the sound barrier being broken.
Do it again, Murr.
I'll show you again, in case you missed it.
Wha-pish!
Did you hear that?
Keep whipping, and whenever we yell "now"
Clap and point to the person on the left.
Q, start shooting air pistols.
Wha-pish!
Pow!
Pow-pow!
Wha-pish!
Now!
Keep going. Keep going.
Yee-haw!
Yahoo!
Pow-pow-pow!
Yee-haw!
Pow-pow!
Pssh! Pssh!
Pow-pssh!
You got that?
We got one more skill to show you here.
"We got Robert coming out."
We got Robert coming out. Robert?
Boys, just go ahead and saddle that horse.
We're gonna show you how to saddle this horse.
Here we are.
Murray, now! Now!
OK, all right. All right.
Good girl. Good girl.
The wind got my hat there. Sorry.
What you do is you take the saddle, and you
I guess you put it over his back?
There you go.
And now, that's backwards, right?
"Let's hear it for Robert."
Let's hear it for Robert, everybody.
Robert and I have a history.
I brought a girl on this ranch once.
I ain't never seen her again.
"Robert doesn't have an earpiece."
Robert has no earpiece.
Offered unprompted.
Thank you. Thank you, Robert.
Out of the five of you, by show of hands
How many of you think you've learned something of value here today?
Come on. How many? How many?
So that's no hands at all?
Zero hands. All right.
Now.
Git along, little dogies.
Oh, my god.
I might believe you, Sal, but Joe does not look like he belongs at all.
Thanks, guys, for coming.
What we do is we show what it's like to be a real cowboy.
They're not gonna fool this guy.
He's like a real cowboy.
Grab that steer.
Set this guy down right here.
Now, Joe, sit on this steer.
So, you're gonna...
Sal, show them how to lasso.
So, OK.
Look at Joe. Look at Joe.
So, here we go, Joe.
Help us all.
You're gonna want to go...
This is not gonna work out well at all.
All right.
Joe, when that rope hits you, fall off the steer.
Now, Sal, fall for no reason.
So, with the lasso, you basically -- you're just gonna hold it out.
You should move away 'cause I don't want to hurt nobody.
And you want to walk around.
Squat down as you're trying to do it.
So, you want -- you want to sneak up on it.
Sneak up on it.
If he doesn't know I'm coming, this longhorn ain't going anywhere.
Sal, grab your lasso and do it, too.
Just sneak up on it. Be really quiet about it.
That looks so stupid.
But you got to keep the rope moving.
I'm gonna get this steer. This one's gonna be mine.
The tree got in the way.
Any questions about the lasso?
You guys got that?
All right, guys, on to the bullwhips now.
We'll show you the bullwhip.
Sal, fall!
Bullwhips.
So, the bullwhip makes a loud whip noise.
Oh, not bad.
He clipped himself.
Ow! [bleep]
Oh, my god! I just jacked myself up!
Now, that is a look of utter disbelief.
One last question that we like to ask everybody.
Just raise your hand if you feel like you learned something new here today.
All right, we'll take two.
So, thank you, guys, very much.
They say you shouldn't tip cows, but you can always tip your cowboy.
Right?
Murr and Q couldn't rope a win
So they're branded up on the loser board.
Coming up -- What's got Murr riding sidesaddle?
And later -- which joker gets dragged into tonight's punishment?
Giddy up, partners. Welcome to Austin.
Today we're shilling boots, buckles, hats
And everything else western at Allens Boots.
While posing as employees
We'll have to do and say what the other cowboys tell us.
And if you refuse, you're getting yourself hogtied.
Hello, bud. How are you doing?
Good. How are you?
Good. Welcome.
Joe, tell him you're in the witness protection program.
Yeah, just let details slip, though.
What are you looking for today?
Browsing around?
Are you from here?
I was from New York. Brooklyn.
OK.
I'm out here now just trying to start over -- new life, new name, new job.
It's not as good as Brooklyn.
I had a lot more friends in Brooklyn, a lot more family.
Yeah.
You know? But I can't talk to them no more.
But it's good.
It's totally different living.
You don't know all the right spots to do stuff, you know?
Like what's the best place to get food
Place to hide a body. You know, any of that stuff.
What I'm saying is I'm in the witness protection.
I had to get it off my chest to somebody. You understand?
I'm a disgraziato. They call me Joey turncoat.
Tell him all the gruesome things you did.
This one time I had to make a guy disappear.
I put chains around his ankles.
I made him hold the bricks.
Jump in the water on his own 'cause that's how I used to get down.
OK.
I make them kill themselves so they can't pin it -- that was the whole.
He couldn't hold it!
Those were the days, man. But now I just sell boots.
Thank you, man.
Murr, you look so out of place in that thing.
There's not one fiber of his being that is anything country or anything cowboy.
You're far more prissier than I am.
I am? Really?
I do self-manicuring more than Sal does
But Sal primps about his clothing and hair far more than I do.
Sal's a big primper.
What does "primper" mean?
"To primp -- spend time making minor adjustment to one's makeup, hair, or clothes."
Yes, that is 100% you.
Oh [bleep]. I do primp.
Guilty as charged.
Murr?
Mm.
Go to the aisle where the hats are and help that couple there.
What kind of hat are you looking for?
Go ahead, partner, put some hats on her.
Let me see. OK.
Want to try this style on you.
Now, hats run in pretty standard sizes.
That one's too big for you, right? That's way too big.
So let's try the other one instead of that one.
Oh, no.
Just start stacking the hats on her head.
Let's try one of these on.
Keep going. Keep going.
The great thing about these is that...
Murr, just throw one.
Um... they're not as good as the black ones.
So, you want to wrap these up?
Murr, go help that mom and her kid.
Hi, guys. If you need any help, I'm the man to ask, OK?
You can have a seat.
We'll bring them right out, and you can try them on, see if you like them.
"You know, I only do this part time."
I only do this part time, though.
"I'm actually in a rap group called Cowboyz with a 'z'".
I'm actually -- I'm also -- my other gig is I'm in a hip-hop group called Cowboyz, with a "Z."
Z?
Yeah.
"Let me show you one of our raps right now."
Do you want to hear one of our raps?
You know I do.
"This one's called 'We Dogy'"
Wha-- this one's called... "We Dogy"
Good luck.
Get into it. Get into it. Own it.
♪ We doggies don't you know?
He's down! He's down!
That's the -- I've only got the first line.
We got him! We got him!
You can't do it. That's it. You're out!
Thumbs down.
Sal, the guy with the lollipop.
Yes, sir. How are you?
Belts? I mean, we have everything here that you see.
Measure everything on his body.
The belts stretch proportionally to how your body uses it.
You want to make sure you measure properly.
You do nipple to pocket.
And then you do shoulder to knee.
And then you do ear to tip of nose like that.
Well, because we custom-fit them.
What does that mean? What does that even mean?
And then if you go from the back over the...
And this is gonna be about 60.
Keep measuring. Keep measuring, man.
You want to go around it like that, just to see...
Sal, the next person that walks through that door
You want to give them a big Texas welcome.
OK.
Yeah. You're just gonna say, "howdy [bleep]"
Big Texas welcome!
Ooh. "Howdy [bleep]"
Here you go. Coming in! Coming in!
Oh, no.
Sal, the next person that walks through that door
You want to give them a big Texas welcome.
OK.
Yeah. You're just gonna say, "howdy [bleep]"
Here you go. Coming in! Coming in!
Oh, no.
Howdy [bleep]
I don't believe you did it. I don't believe you did it.
I ain't losing in Texas.
Q.
Yeah?
You see this guy walking down the aisle?
Go in the other aisle and push boots out toward this guy.
"We can't keep these boots on the shelves."
"With prices like these."
Do you need help with anything, sir, or are you good?
Oh, you're admiring them?
Yeah
This one's my favorite.
All the Luccheses look good.
I love that one.
These look good.
I love them, you know what I mean?
Oh, my god, it looks like "Ghostbusters."
I'll just show you one more.
Cleanup, Aisle Six.
"Do I look familiar to you?"
Excuse me.
Do I look familiar to you at all?
Oh, you've never been here before.
"Not from this job."
Not from this job.
"Thursday nights, I dance at Milking Studs, the strip club down on Route 9."
'Cause... Thursday night, I dance at
uh...this male strip club called Milking Studs.
Yeah, I could've sworn that you bought a dance from me.
Oh, OK, OK.
Just start peeling your vest off slow. Take your vest off.
Ah, well, we, you know...
Yeah, and grind the hips a little, buddy.
You know, we do -- we have a good sale selection.
Unbutton one at a time.
It looks like you're constipated.
Show her the butt!
You see what you're doing? You're 37 years old.
Oh, he's got the strut.
Murr couldn't bust a rhyme, so on the loser board, he's doing time.
We're at the Tejas Rodeo Pavilion
Just moseying around with our sunglasses on.
Except these sunglasses have been blacked out on the inside
So we can't see a blessed thing.
The other guys will tell us what to say, what to do, and where to move.
You'll have to do what you're told and then deal with the consequences.
If you can't, you lose.
Hey, cowboys, it all comes down to this!
Here I go.
Oh, my god.
Murr, walk straight.
To the right, to the right, to the right. OK, straight from there.
Watch your step.
Murr, you're on the moon.
Go straight. Go straight.
What is this?
Get on. Get on. Get on.
Wasn't that fun?
Take your glasses off.
[bleep] It's a damn bull! [bleep] Jerks! [bleep]
That was great.
Nice work, boys.
Left, left, left, left, left.
"Excuse me, sir."
Excuse me, sir.
"Ma'am."
Ma'am.
"You guys clearly remember the Alamo, huh?"
You guys cl-- Oh, man.
He's never gonna say it. He's never gonna say it.
I bet you he does.
Bet you he doesn't.
Well, I bet you he does.
If he says it, I'll take a loss on the whole episode.
That's how [bleep] positive I know he's not gonna say this.
You clearly remember the Alamo, right?
Why would you think that he's not gonna say it?
He doesn't know who he's talking to, you f-- idiot.
Nice to meet you. Thanks for talking.
Murr, you made something amazing happen back here.
What happened?
Q took a loss on the whole episode.
He bet you wouldn't say it.
Oh, my god. Are you kidding me?
Why would you even say that?
I didn't think he was gonna say it!
You got to stay out of the saloon, buddy.
Q put his boot in his mouth, so he's tonight's big loser.
Q just made the worst bet of his life.
What are you doing?!
I'm an idiot.
Q had the episode in the bag and is now the loser.
So we're here at the Texas Rodeo
And all you got to do is go out there and rope a calf.
So, that's it, buddy. You're a rodeo champ.
You got to get out there, tell them about your rodeo skills
And then show them your rodeo skills.
Everything's bigger in Texas, especially the loser.
These people watching, they're watching real cowboys and cowgirls do their thing.
Then here comes Q from Staten Island, New York.
I don't stand a chance.
Let this be a lesson to you to not make stupid bets that don't make any sense.
Here it come. Here you go.
It's you, buddy.
Howdy, y'all.
I'm Brian Quinn. How are you guys?
I'm from a little place called Staten Island, New York... City, that is.
And you guys may not know this
But we have the rodeo up there, too.
No, we don't.
And I'm an expert at it.
We all know that rodeo is the act of sitting on an animal that doesn't want to be sat on.
And I do that well.
I usually sit on animals until I become the champion.
Who am I?
"I'm rodeo champion of the world."
I'm rodeo champion of the world!
Can I get a rope and hand this off to someone?
All right, buddy, go rope a calf.
Thanks, bud.
OK. Oh, OK.
All right. Got it.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Got it.
He corrected the way to hold the rope! He wasn't even --
All right, cow.
I love animals.
I love you.
I would never hurt you in a billion years.
You don't hurt me.
Here's the part Q doesn't know about -- Texas justice.
Whoa! Whoa! What the hell are you doing?!
What are you doing?!
Get the hell away from me! Get the --
Whoa!
What are you doing? Don't --
Are you kidding me?
Are you [bleep] kidding me?
What are you doing?
I'm gonna kill you.
Champion of the world!
Yes!
"It ain't New York anymore."
Yee-haw!
Well, that is Texas.