Coming up, why are Sal and Q hitting the bottle?
Will Murr finally step up to the plate?
How do I get to first base?
It's normally up here.
And which joker will have to clean house after tonight's punishment?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Today we are giving personality tests to strangers.
However, the person really being tested is us.
While giving the survey, the other guys will be behind this glass wall
which becomes see-through at the flip of a switch.
The goal is not to laugh.
And when that glass becomes see-through, anything goes...
I'm fascinated by that glass.
When we thought of this bit, we had no idea this technology existed.
Is that, like, ions? Is that negatively charged ions?
I think it's magic.
Hello. Hi.
Elizabeth.
Elizabeth. Oh, please, have a seat, Elizabeth.
How are you today?
Good.
So, I'll just be asking you questions.
Let's go.
Where are you from?
I grew up in St. Louis.
You live in New York City?
Yeah, so I'm based here now.
So, tell me about your daily eating habits.
They've gotten better.
I used to eat more junk food, but I'm...
You go -- you shop in the same place every week?
Yeah, I go -- I have this -- I like Italian at this one place.
That's just namaste.
What sort of -- what social-media sites are you a member of?
Twitter, Facebook.
Do you have cable?
I do.
How long have you had cable for?
Um, gosh.
Since, like, college.
So I always had a cable internet connection.
I'm a techie, so, like, I hook -- instead of having, like, cable...
Oh, my god!
Sorry. Do you prefer to shop alone or with someone?
Don't do that. Don't turn around. Don't.
Sorry. There's a fly.
Oh.
There's -- a bug got in here.
It looked like it was gonna land on your head. I didn't...
OK.
Wow! Things are getting real in here.
All right, you guys are up.
So, luxury brands.
So, I had a wallet before this one, and then, once I had that one for five years...
So I kind of like stick with it.
OK.
Oh, my god.
Do your friends use it?
Do -- I mean, not, like, often, like...
Because economically speaking, they don't have the same, I guess, income resources as I do.
So I think they would love to if they could afford it.
Movies -- we didn't talk about movies yet, right?
Thank god.
How did you not laugh?
OK, how often do you go to the movies?
It's usually, I mean, twice a month...
It's -- it's Godzilla!
...or as much as once a week.
Oh, my god!
Uh... what's the last movie you saw?
"Wolf of Wall Street."
He's laughing.
Hi. I'm James Murray. How are you?
Have a seat, please.
Murr, welcome to your worst nightmare.
OK. First, some general questions.
When you eat on vacation, do you keep to your diet that you may have at home?
No.
You don't?
It's Murr the puppet. It's a "Murr-pet."
Are you a member of a gym at all?
No.
He wishes it was a real boy.
Oh, look. It's a fairy godmother.
Ding!
...I don't need a gym to do.
Tell me about what your exercise routine was or would be.
Oh, look, it's a Murr.
Same pencil neck.
Same hairline.
Oh, my god. That's what Murr would look like if he grew a mullet.
Tell me what -- what motivates you on vacation?
The relaxation.
Relaxation's number 1?
Hey, just two friends hanging out.
Love you, man. Love you.
No, don't get -- no, you're friends. Don't fight.
Sal really got jacked!
So, tell me -- tell me about --
Tell me about -- have you ever taken a cruise before?
No.
It really hurts!
You've never been on a cruise?
No.
No? OK.
Why are you laughing so much?
That felt weird to do.
That was weird.
It felt weird to do.
It looked weird to do. All right, let me give it a shot.
Let's switch topics a little bit.
Tell me about your daily routines.
Take me through a typical Saturday.
OK. I try to do as little as humanly possible and just sleep more.
I prepare all my meals, usually.
I don't... buy food from outside.
And I might meet up with my friends.
Uh-huh. What do you do on a typical Saturday night?
Usually, go drinking or stay home.
What was that?
Doughnuts?
Oh, my god! It's doughnuts!
Look at his face.
There he goes. That's a laugh.
Oh, my god! It's doughnuts!
Wow. Murr. You got him again.
Hey, Sal, this is what the kids call a walk in the park.
We have to get you to laugh.
You guys all talk a good game. You all keep talking this good game.
You watch. Look at me. Ready?
Yeah.
Watch this.
Fart noise.
I didn't even make the fart noise -- I said the words "fart noise."
That's what was funny about it.
Hey, how are you, bud?
What's going on? My name's Sal.
Zachary? Pleasure to meet you.
Let me go help this guy.
Yeah, go get him, tiger.
How often do you feel the need to update your software and things like that kind of stuff?
I mean, I have a laptop, but I really don't use it anymore
because of the new technology like the smartphones and things like that.
As far as -- sorry.
I'm trying to think, 'cause we go through all the things you ever got.
Oh, it's not over yet, buddy.
This is gonna haunt your dreams, my friend.
Talk to me about your opinions on the subway system.
Depending on public transportation, as far as --
There's a lot of idiotic people that's on the train
that does stupid things just to hold the train door, so...
... for no reason at all.
They have nothing better to do or anywhere -- anywhere else to go.
I know.
They do have good plans for public transportation and a good...
Oh, my god!
Someone's system sucks.
The train is awful.
Yeah, as far as getting around to the, like, different boroughs.
I'm next.
Let's see what I got up my sleeve.
Just please elaborate on...
Q has guaranteed us that he's got this. I trust him.
He's got it.
Do you online bank?
Yes, I do.
OK.
It's your father... marrying Q!
He's not giving him away.
Bridegroom kissed the bride.
Oh, we're done. We're done here. We're done here.
All right, Joey, you're up. How do you feel out there?
Stone-cold killer.
No way.
Look at that.
Pleased to meet you. Have a seat, my friend.
Let's go turn the screws on this, huh?
Tell me about a typical movie experience for you.
Do you buy the tickets online?
Oh, no, I buy the tickets at the machine.
At the machine?
Yeah.
OK. Wow. All right.
Do you ever go to the YMCA?
No.
No. You don't go to the YMCA?
Uh... would you consider yourself accepting any friends?
Let's say you have three best friends, and other people might think they're, you know [bleep]
But they're your friends.
When you have a group party, are you likely or not likely to bring out a board game?
Depends on the party.
If it's, like, during the day...
It's a cute old lady.
Look at Joe's curious, confused face.
Oh, what's gonna happen to her?
What's gonna happen?
OK. Do you -- do you calorie-count?
Oh, my god.
Oh, don't do it.
Oh. There you go.
Oh, my god!
I did not see that coming.
This is just insane.
You got to give it to them. You got to give it to them, man.
Q, Murr, and Sal are all laughers, making them all losers.
Today, we'll be stopping strangers and starting a conversation with a single word.
But that word is gonna be given to us by the other guys.
And that word won't make sense until we're given the explanation afterward.
The goal is to follow through with the surprise explanation.
If you can't, you lose, and I don't know what this is.
It's a ponytail. I'm trying something new, all right?
You know what I often think about, boys?
Doughnuts?
You guys know me.
Excuse me.
"Sexy?"
Sexy?
"That's my nickname for my sister."
That, uh, that's the nickname I call my sister.
You know what I'm saying?
She got an ass that won't quit. I'm just saying.
All day with it.
Excuse me.
"Ozone?"
Ozone?
"Oh, I'm sorry. I meant, 'I want to touch you in your boy zone.'"
That went over my head.
I'm sorry. I meant to say...
I meant to say, "I want to touch you in your boy zone."
And you would say...
I would probably kill you.
You would probably kill me. All right. Good.
Where is this going?
I think we're done with it.
You got a good day.
Take care, buddy. Take care of yourself.
All right, you ready, my little pony?
Thank you, thank you.
She complimented my ponytail.
They didn't say anything.
Thank you, guys. Thanks for the compliment on my ponytail.
You know, I haven't heard one person.
You like the ponytail? Thank you, sir!
Excuse me.
"Ponytail."
Ponytail.
"Look at this [bleep] stupid ponytail."
Look at this [bleep] stupid ponytail.
Yeah, I heard that one.
Excuse me one second. Um...
"Baby."
Baby.
"That's what I'm gonna put into you."
That's what I'm -- baby -- that's what I'm gonna put into you, huh?
Got it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Another compliment on my ponytail, boys.
No one has said, "nice ponytail."
I've heard "nice ponytail" three times.
You look out of touch, man.
Excuse me.
"Directions?"
Directions? Um...
"How do I get to first base?"
How do -- how do I get to first base?
What do you mean?
I can't find my way. I keep -- I keep making the wrong turns.
To first base?
I don't know where first base is.
It's normally up here.
Yeah. The -- the -- the -- the -- the -- the tea-- the teats.
The teats.
I think I just figured out why you can't get there -- you're calling them "teats."
I feel so bad for his future son when they're gonna have that talk.
Thanks so much, man. You, too.
He's walking away shaking his head.
Excuse me.
"Three."
Three.
"You two plus me."
You two plus me... is three.
We doing this or what?
No?
Is it -- is it me, or is it him?
It's me.
It's you. OK.
I had to ask. OK.
These two guys. "You"
You, you, you, you, you, you. You.
"Suck."
So...
What, man?
Say it, say it!
... are awesome. Have a great day.
Come on.
Two words -- one thumbs-down.
Hey.
"Hungary."
Hungary.
Huh?
"That's where my bride's being shipped from."
No, no, no. Not that "hungry."
That's where my bride's being shipped from.
I was told to wait right here for her.
I hope she's the good-looking European.
Oh, this girl.
"Zero."
Zero?
"That's my chances with you?"
Zero is -- those are my chances with you?
I don't know what -- what came over me there.
Probably three 37-year-old men.
Yes.
"Fire."
Excuse me. Fire? Fire?
"That's what it feels like when I make peeps."
That's actually what it feels like when I make -- when I make peeps.
Now she knows you have an std.
Good work, buddy.
The key word for Murr is "loser!" which means it's punishment time.
Hey! Here we are.
Murr is our loser, and now it's time to be punished.
All right, buddy.
You're gonna to go in there and pitch your new television show that we've created.
And you'll be showing it to the TV show's target audience, 8-year-olds.
So, kiddies. I don't do well with children.
Hi, everybody.
Hi. I'm James.
You having fun today?
What looks like me?
"Murr's play house."
That does look like me.
There's a questionnaire behind you, bud, right on that windowsill.
OK.
Just grab that.
OK. Here's a questionnaire. I'm gonna ask you guys a couple questions, OK?
So, we're leaving here.
We're not gonna be here.
We're actually gonna take this time to go to Murray's apartment, which is nearby and destroy it.
And the trick of it is we're going to play that live
on that little television he has set up in that room, so...
Ladies and gentlemen, we're proud to present "Murr's play house" at his real play house.
We better get moving, guys. We got three blocks to cover.
What's the grossest thing you can think of?
What smells funny?
Your English teacher?
Ah! That's funny.
Guys, are you there? It's really quiet.
OK, there's one more question, and nothing's happened.
I'm a little confused right now.
What's your favorite holiday, out of all the holidays -- Easter, Christmas...
Christmas!
Christmas? OK.
Hi, guys!
Hey! Welcome to "Murr's play house"!
Look where we are.
It's so much fun here in Murr's play house.
So, hey, Murr, how are you, buddy?
Wait, this is happening live?
Yeah, it's live.
Yeah, we hear you.
Wait. This is now?!
Yeah, this is right now.
This is real?
It's right now!
No, no. This is not actually happening, right? That's my apartment!
Get the hell out of my apartment!
That's where the delay was...
Why don't you grab those questions that are behind the TV
and ask the kiddies what they want to see?
OK, the first question --
Should the guys have a serious talk or a silly string fight?
Silly string fight, silly string fight...
Oh, no! It's all over the place!
I-I-I pride myself on keeping my apartment really clean.
What's next, kids?
Uh... should the guys play a flute or play frisbee with a pizza?
Frisbee with a pizza!
Ohhh, god. No.
I have beige couches.
Time to play frisbee pizza.
I got it.
Ready, Q?
I'm ready!
Right back at you, buddy!
Oh! I missed it! Oh, no!
Oh, I missed it.
Oh, it's on the rug!
Oh, you're stepping on the frisbee.
Hey, kids.
Oh, god.
What's next?
Should crazy Steve read a story or take a crazy bubble bath?
Take a crazy bubble bath!
Bubble bath...
Hey, crazy Steve.
Hi, kids.
Oh, my god. He's gross.
Oh, my god!
It's so soapy in here.
Oh, my god. He's so hairy.
Let's go. What else do you got, bud?
Uh, I don't think -- I don't -- I don't think anybody wants to see any other questions.
Yes, we do!
All right, next question --
Do you want the guys to clean the toilet... or do you want them to feed the toilet?
Feed the toilet!
The toilet only eats dress clothes.
Dress clothes.
But wait right here.
I just got these out of the closet.
No, no, no, no, no. Don't you -- don't you dare.
Don't you dare.
Are you hungry?
Why, yes, I am hungry.
I just -- I just got them steamed one week ago.
Toilet!
I eat dress clothes!
Oh, no. I can't even -- I can't even say bad words.
Isn't Murr's play house so much fun?
Yeah, it's fun!
OK, guys. The next question is...
I'm not reading the next question.
Just do it! Do it!
I'm not reading the question.
It's a punishment.
I'm not gonna read this question.
Read it!
Hey, kids, do you want us to take a nap, or do you want us to smash a television?!
Smash the TV!
Well, look what I have right here!
It's the super-duper smasher sledgehammer!
Guys, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
That's not funny.
1...
Oh, god!
...2 ...3!
We smashed your TV!
I can't get enough of smashing this TV!
Kids, thank you coming to Murr's play house.
Stay in school.
Bye, everybody.
I'm gonna kick some ass.