Coming up, why is Joe fighting for his life?
It's a knockout!
What's got Murr heading for disaster.
Regular coffee.
And will tonight's big loser be the ring bearer of bad news?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Today we are dumb waiters.
No, that's an old-fashioned pulley system.
Today, we're old-fashioned pulley systems?
No!
Today, we are waiters at the Carnegie Deli.
While serving customers, we must do and say what we're told.
If you refuse, you lose.
So, we're losers?
Yes, all right.
How do I do this?
He's a 37-year-old grown man
Getting instruction on how to put an apron on.
Murr, it works the same as a traditional apron that was invented thousands of years ago.
Yes, sir.
Here we go, here we go.
What do you need?
Murray, switch their two plates.
Let me get it for you.
Ketchup for...
Oh, for the fries.
Sure, let me get it for you. One sec.
Murr, you got to correct those plates again.
They keep finding their way over to the wrong spot.
Here you go, guys.
Did you need anything else at all?
OK. There you go. Enjoy, guys.
She's still got the fork in her hand with the ham.
You got to switch it one more time, Murr.
Excuse me, folks. There you go.
Oh, my god.
Yes! Three times!
He's just eating it!
The guy gave up. He's just eating it.
Hi, folks. Are you ready to place your order?
Murr, rest your notepad on the top of her head while you take the order.
Pastrami sandwich.
Pastrami sandwich? And, uh...
You said you wanted a knish, right?
You got to write on the notepad against the head.
Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
And, sir, did you want anything to drink?
Yeah, I'll have a coffee.
A coffee? OK.
Oh! He did it!
Regular coffee?
I don't know what to do with this guy.
Great. I'll take those. Thank you so much.
That was tough.
I got to give it up to you, buddy.
Joey
Yep.
You ready?
Yeah, guys. Ready to go.
Joe!
I love days like today.
How are you not dead?
Thank you, guys. Thanks for coming.
All right, put the cake down. Get out there, you idiot.
Are you guys all together or...?
Oh, no. You're by yourself?
Joe, make sure she knows she's alone.
You're alone?
"Got stood up or...?"
Did you get stood up?
No.
Oh, traveling by yourself. Good for you.
"Do you want me to take that extra chair away
so it's not a constant reminder that you're alone?"
Um, I can move that chair if you'd like
so you don't have a constant reminder that you're by yourself.
That's OK there?
And then you have the pickles.
Are you gonna eat all those pickles? Because, again, you're by yourself.
Come on. Hammer it home, Joe.
And do you want separate checks?
Oh, I'm sorry. You're all by yourself, so it'll just be you.
How you doing?
Tell these people the specials, and after every item, say the word "tit."
You are so stupid, really.
We're known mostly for our pastrami tit.
Um, they're known for --
A pastrami what?
I'm sorry?
What'd you call it?
Pastrami tit.
Tit?
Yeah.
That's the lingo here.
You got the roast-beef tit, you got the pastrami tit.
You could get yourself a corned-beef tit.
Did you guys want some coleslaw tit and pickle tit to start?
That comes complimentary to the table.
Sure.
Sal, the camouflage shirt -- they need a refill of water.
OK.
Every cup on the table fill up with water.
Oh, this is tea.
"Please stop yelling at me, sir."
Please -- please stop yelling at me.
Huh?
Please stop yelling at me.
OK, buddy, explain yourself.
I'm just really sensitive. Um...
I -- I deal with a lot of people out here all day long
And a lot of them don't really care for me.
I'm trying to fill up some water
just so you guys have a more pleasant experience.
I mean, you guys aren't even looking at me right now.
I'm like a second-rate citizen?
I'm just worried about your hydration.
Oh, my god. You guys are [bleep]
Sal, right there -- write a note.
"I like you."
"Do you like me?"
And make three check boxes underneath -- yes, no, and maybe.
So, bring that lady's sandwich over and just also drop off the note.
OK, ladies, here you go. It's the roast beef with tomato.
"And then this is for you."
OK. And then this is... I'm gonna give it over here to you.
Oh, my gosh.
Sal, go back and get the note.
All right. Still got it.
And what else can I get for you?
Just one herbal tea?
Just put your pen in your nose.
Far enough that you could leave it there without holding it.
Yeah, take your hand off.
And anything for you?
Nothing?
Now just put the pen in your mouth, buddy.
Is that a no?
Just one herbal tea?
OK.
Do it now.
I'm not putting the pen in my mouth.
Right up on the ear.
Buddy, you're up.
Here we go, Q.
Yeah, I thought about this one.
If it's all right, I'm gonna take a pass today.
You can't take a pass.
I brought a friend to go for me.
Oh, a sub?
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah. My friend. You guys hear of 'N Sync?
How did you get Joey Fatone to take your place?
We go way back!
No, you don't! We go way back!
If he fails, you take the loss.
I'm willing to live or die... by the hands of Joey Fatone.
I will try my hardest.
You know what I feel?
I'm nervous, like that someone's just gonna punch the [bleep] out of me.
You got it, buddy. I got all the faith of you in the world.
All right, Joey, so, take a walk into the restaurant.
Keep walking straight. There's that Asian woman. She's eating. See her?
Mm-hmm.
She's done. You can take her plate.
I'm gonna throw up right now. I swear to god.
Don't [bleep] this up for me, all right?
This should be interesting. Fatone's in for Q.
All right, you got my back now, Fatone, right?
All right, Joey, so, take a walk into the restaurant.
Keep walking straight. There's that Asian woman. She's eating. See her?
Mm-hmm.
She's done. You can take her plate.
I'm gonna throw up right now. I swear to god.
You guys are enjoying yourselves? You guys are OK?
Could we get a couple more slices of bread?
Some more bread?
All right, cool. You good with this? Thank you.
She's not done.
Joey, there's a gentleman sitting down with a gray shirt.
See how their meal's going, OK?
You guys OK? Everybody's all right?
Reach over and put your right hand in his corned beef.
Excuse me, how good is that though?
Do it, do it, do it.
It's like -- I mean, it's really good.
Oh, my god!
And don't forget to tip the waitress, all right?
You son of a bitch! He's unbeatable!
This is an instant upgrade here. Q wouldn't have done that.
That is why he is in for me right now.
Joe, OK, last thing. Ready?
I just want you to yell
"Hello, everyone! I'm Joey Fatone.
You should all know I just [bleep] my pants!"
Hey, everybody, can I have your attention, please?
My name is Joey Fatone... and I just [bleep] my pants.
Unbelievable.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
I can't believe he did it!
Joey, I want to say thank you, my friend.
Because of you, I'm getting the thumbs up.
Looks like Sal got served, so he's first up on the loser board.
Today, we're working at a deli trying to figure out who's the best debater.
We're going head-to-head, tournament style
trying to get customers to settle the most ridiculous of debates.
But the topic of the debate will be given to us by the other guys
The goal is to get the customer to agree with your stance, no matter how bizarre it is.
If you can't get the customer to say you're right, you lose.
Let's get out of the street, guys.
Yeah. Why are we in the street?
You have an advantage here, you know.
—I worked in a deli for many years.   —You worked at a deli, behind this counter.
Murr, his advantage is that you're an idiot.
I'm telling you, buddy, I've been thinking about this all day.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you settle a quick debate for us?
Of course I can.
Ah, here we go.
What is your name?
My name's Darius.
We've been having this debate for an hour now.
OK, bring it on.
"Who had it more embarrassing?"
Who had it more embarrassing?
I say it was the way I lost my virginity.
Sal, "I say it was the way I lost my virginity."
It was definitely the way that I lost my virginity.
Tell the stories, boys.
Uh, well, I lost my virginity, first of all, a year ago.
I'm 37.
And it was to my wife.
It was to your wife, who is now your wife?
We've been married for 15 years.
And you hadn't yet done the deed?
Not yet done the deed.
There's no way you beat him.
Wait!
All right, go.
OK. Embarrassing, for sure.
I'll give you that.
Married for that many years...
Stalling, stalling, stalling.
Vamping for time
The way I lost mine is far more embarrassing.
I mean, look, I'm not even listening to that.
The editorializing, I don't even hear it.
I love this guy!
I love you!
He saw your [bleep]
About 10 years ago, I went on a trip to Las Vegas
and I was in one of these super-duper pools that has this very strong current.
I got pulled into the current, my bathing suit got ripped off, and my...
ding-dong got pulled into the pool filter.
Look at Sal.
When they brought me to the hospital, the doctor said
that that is actually, technically, how I lost my virginity.
I love this guy.
I was humping a pool filter at the Bellagio.
That doesn't matter. You didn't have the vagina, my friend.
Oh, my gosh!
This is straight-up [bleep] man.
No, I'm sorry.
Thank you, Darius.
Yeah, he's out!
Son of a...
You didn't have the vagina, my friend.
Sal is moving on.
Joe vs Q, here we go.
Put your feet away.
I'm cracking my toes, man.
I know, but other people are around you.
There they go, there they go.
And you keep touching your balls.
There's the debate -- why are we friends?
Keep scratching your crotch.
This is the debate downstairs. It's flipped.
Now look at us. We're buddy-buddy.
We're having a blast over here.
These two idiots are downstairs fighting in my ear.
What I do in my cubic space is my own decision.
You're wrong. You know who you are?
You're the guy who [bleep] eats spaghetti on the train.
I am that guy.
All right, guys, we got somebody.
Could you help us settle a debate real quick?
We're having this debate all day.
All day.
"What's the better way to die?"
What's the better way to die?
"I'd rather get kicked to death by a giraffe."
I say get kicked to death by a giraffe.
Q, "I'd rather get trapped by a bunch of celery."
I'd rather get trapped under a big piece of celery and die that way.
Giraffe, they got the long legs.
That hoof is gonna come in and just conk you.
A giant piece of celery just...pck!
You know, the giraffe's walking along, doing its thing, and it gives you one good punch.
If this celery falls on you, you can live in it like a tunnel for a while.
Let's not rush the death, people.
How much celery can I eat to get out?
Celery does have fiber, so you're gonna be...
You know what doesn't have fiber or water in it?
A [bleep] giraffe hoof right to the face.
You don't want to be trapped in a giant's garden under his piece of celery?
That's not how you want to go?
You want the giraffe to come in hot and just keep pounding you!
Comes up...
How am I supposed to compete with a giraffe?
It's the giraffe.
Yes! Death by giraffe!
Sorry, buddy, it's a knockout!
All right, Joe's moving on.
Here we go, final round, Joe vs Sal.
Winner takes all.
You want to help us settle a debate, my friend?
Here they go.
OK. So you're our judge and jury, OK?
Here's the debate.
"Who's more powerful?"
Who's more powerful?
Sal, you say batman is more powerful.
I think, hands down, batman.
Versus?
Joe, you think Jesus is more powerful.
OK. So you're our judge and jury, OK?
Final round. Winner takes all.
Here's the debate.
"Who's more powerful?"
Who's more powerful?
Sal, you say batman is more powerful.
I think, hands down, batman.
Versus?
Joe, you think Jesus is more powerful.
Jesus.
Batman is the caped crusader.
He is trained in the martial arts.
I mean, he protects an entire city.
Am I right or am I right?
I agree with that, but I would also say that Jesus was able to move the masses.
Was Jesus the powerful one or was it god?
Then you could say, "was it batman's suit vs batman?"
Oh. Now my man is helping me out.
That's true, but people don't go, "oh, my Jesus."
They say, "oh, my god."
Yeah, but they don't say, "oh, my batman."
Jesus has one book. Batman has thousands of comics.
Jesus only needs one book 'cause he's that powerful.
You walk out, a street tough approaches you out there, OK?
You're looking both ways
Hoping Jesus runs down the block in his sandals and his toga?
Or are you hoping that the caped crusader
In a batsuit comes down with a batarang and does some damage?
You're saying to fight force with force, right?
Yes.
Jesus would just be peaceful.
And that's real power!
But who is more powerful?
Let's be honest -- I never had a chance, did i?
Sal loses yet again.
What a bunch of holy [bleep]
Kapow!
Sal, Murr, and Q lost, making it a dark night for Sal.
Sal's our big loser.
So, to celebrate, we're here at Gary and Crystal's wedding.
OK. Who's Gary and Crystal?
Ah, don't worry about that, Sal.
You should worry about the speech.
No! No, no, no, no, no, guys...
Just go out there and speak from the heart.
No, I can't.
That's fine. We didn't think you could, so we wrote this speech for you.
Go ahead. Go out there and give a little speech.
We got you all taken care of.
Look at him.
Look how nervous he is.
All right, here he goes.
Oh, my god. Look at this.
There's a lot of people in that wedding, buddy.
This is not -- this is not right.
This is not right.
What Sal doesn't know is the bride and groom are actually in on it.
Yes.
But the 300 strangers in the room are a different story.
Definitely not in on it.
We're gonna ruin this wedding.
Here it comes.
All right, buddy, next speech is all yours, pal.
Cheers!
Here we go. Yes.
Hello, everyone.
Here we go, here we go.
I hate you guys.
Oh, you hate us? I'm sorry you are hating us.
Cheers!
Here it comes.
All right, buddy, next speech is all yours, pal.
Hello, everyone.
What Sal doesn't know is the bride and groom are actually in on it.
Yes.
But the 300 strangers in the room are a different story.
Definitely not in on it.
Crystal and Gary have always been the most good people I've ever known.
They have always been there for me when I needed them.
They're like loyal dogs. They're like my dogs.
Know what I mean?
"Know what I mean?"
So it's fitting that they stood by me when things got... rough-rough.
When I first met them, I used to ask Gary all the time if I could...
I used to ask Gary all the time if he could send me some...
pictures of Crystal in a bikini.
I run a project where I bring pictures of all different girls in bikinis to
prisoners in exchange for woodworkings.
Speaking in bartending speak
I can give you this metaphor about marriage.
The man is like the liquor and the woman is like the mixer.
And life stirs it up, and god is like the bartender.
And -- and the devil -- Mm.
Say it!
The devil is your mother-in-law.
Life's gonna play tricks on you.
You'll lose your job, you'll fight, you'll go into debt, you'll get sick.
So let's raise a glass.
Yeah! Raise a glass!
But he's not done yet!
These two people love each other so much, I hate it.
They slowly lower down.
This isn't a Jewish wedding
But my Jewish friend, Hyman
Told me that, in his culture, it's important for the groom to break a glass.
I'm no Jew, but I have broken a lot of glasses.
But tonight I don't mean to break the Hyman...
Next page!
...tradition.
Look at their faces.
I want to tell you guys something that my grandfather told me
when I was young that gave me the chills.
And it seems most fitting today.
He said, "Sal..."
Here we go, here we go.
"...I shot a lot of Japs in World War II."
Oh, no!
Guys, there's no denying you're awesome together.
But sometimes marriage can be like war.
Don't let the Japanese get in your way.
Oh, my god. They're starting to revolt.
Crystal, you're beautiful insi -- Oh.
Here it comes, here it comes.
I can't say this.
You got to finish that speech, buddy.
You're beautiful inside and out. I should know.
Cheers.
That went over well.
That was brutal, man.
Gentlemen, let's raise a glass.