Are you ready for some exclusive, never-before-seen "Impractical Jokers" clips?
Yes, we are!
That's right.
We went down to the "jokers" vault and pulled out some never-before-seen challenges.
What is "jokers" vault?
It's the place downstairs where we keep all the stuff they've never seen.
You guys have all been to a "jokers" vault?
We're having a crazy party there next weekend.
Yeah, man. I can't wait!
You're having a vault party?
Vault parties!
Am I invited?!
Anyway, stick around towards the end of the episode where we'll show you
what happens when one man finds out that he is on "Impractical Jokers."
And we'll see you at the vault party.
I'll be there.
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Oh, hey ,fellas.
Yeah.
Do you remember when we worked at the pizzeria?
Oh, of course.
Q, get awkwardly close to this guy and just stare into his eyes.
Keep staring.
This guy's looking back into Q's soul.
Yeah, he's not gonna like what he sees.
You know what I'd love to see?
Sal and Joe's unaired turns from that challenge.
Oh, I'd love to see that, too.
Let's see it.
Sal, you worked in a pizzeria for four years?
Yeah.
Does that give you any advantage today?
No.
You know the lingo, the way things are done.
Oh, you mean like "pizza" and "soda"?
How you doing, bud?
Sure. The corners?
Yeah.
All right, Sal, just slap everything that you serve this guy.
Slap it?
Just slap it with your hand.
So you got these two, or you got that one.
One, two, three.
Huh?
This one's not yours?
No, no, I don't want them 'cause you put your hands on them.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's a habit.
The first one's fine, though?
Sal, get your finger in his water.
And then, you got that, and then you got the water here, right.
That's yours.
Hey, how are you?
Sal, everything they say, say "Again with this [bleep]"
Let me get two slices. Yeah, one of these.
Again with this [bleep]
To go or to stay?
Stay.
Do it again.
And you want to heat one of these up for here, right?
Again with this [bleep]
How you doing, bud?
This one?
Yeah.
Sal, grab his hand, and scoop it right into his hand.
Don't use the cup at all.
Uh, it's just two bucks.
Oh, let me see.
Do you want two scoops or one?
Two scoops? Medium?
He stayed there for the second scoop.
Yeah, like, at one, you'd be like, "Dude."
As long as you do something with confidence...
...they're like, "Am I the crazy one?"
I'll tell you what I noticed from that clip is the way you and I say "water" is horrible.
"Wata."
"Wata. Oh, you want some wata?
Put your finger in that wata.
How do you spell "water"?
W-a-t-a.
It's weird.
When I'm not around you, I have an English accent.
It's very bizarre.
Sal, turn away for a second.
Well, hello.
Jolly good. Eh, what's going on around here?
Okay, we saw mine. Why don't we watch Joe's?
What kind of weird pizza-making is that?
Hi, can I help you?
Could I just have a regular slice?
One regular slice?
Dom, one regular slice.
Joe, hit the dough and yell out ethnicities.
Mexicans.
Oh, no, it's just a little bit of everybody.
Everybody today's busting my hump.
Filipinos.
Do you want garlic knots?
Ukrainians.
Che si dice, my man. What's up?
Can I have a vanilla chip?
Joe, nose the ice.
What's the other flavor?
Rainbow.
Really deep.
He's looking at him.
Salute.
Hi, can I help you? What do you need?
Joe, keep looking out the window like Godzilla's coming.
One slice of pizza?
Is that Godzilla outside?
Did you want a lot of ice or a little bit of ice?
Godzilla's getting close, buddy.
Joe, you're too scared to move.
Oh, oh. Holy [bleep]
So, that's $4.75.
Joe, what -- what is that? What?
So, you only need two of --
Oh, there was something coming out of that window, man.
What's that?
I want to go just back to that guy for a second.
He didn't ask for a new ice.
No.
He gave that ice to the person.
You got your nose, you --
I was smelling rainbows for a week and a half.
Stick with us 'cause when we come back
we'll take a look at Q and Murr's turn as janitors in a food court.
Straight from the vault.
What is this vault?
Hey, we're back, and we're taking a look at
never-before-seen clips from this "Impractical Jokers" vault.
The vault, man. That's where we keep all this.
You guys remember when we were at our favorite place,
working as janitors -- the food court?
Oh, yeah!
Sal, tape the fork to the end of your broom, and eat off somebody's plate.
Oh, my god, there he goes!
Oh, he got one!
We know what Joe and I did there.
Look at Q.
It looks like the opening credits to, like, a bad '90s horror movie called "The Custodian."
Q, see this couple eating?
Kneel down, and lean into them.
And I want you to, like, tell them a secret I'm about to tell you.
Folks, folks, folks.
"Did you hear the story of the little girl who ate here last week?"
Did you guys hear the story of the little girl who ate here last week?
No?
Okay. Tell them, buddy.
Yeah, the little girl, that's right, who ate here last week.
Turns out that, uh, she was 18.
So, I totally... hit it.
Turned out she was 18, which is legal.
Wait, he just winked!
Go over to the couple.
Your trash bin's a little full, Q.
How 'bout you empty garbage onto the table instead of taking it off?
Keep going. Keep going.
Her eyes are, like, bulging out of her head.
They are both using the "I'm busy sipping, I don't notice this" defense.
I do like that they reverted to the "What? We're just sipping.
What's happening around us?"
Much like what my parents did with me my entire childhood.
"How long till it goes away?"
Your parents had 25 years of just sipping through straws?
"What should we do about our son?"
"Don't worry about it, honey."
All right. Now let's see what Murr got into when he was a janitor.
All right, Murr, these three guys, their table's dirty, ain't it?
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I don't think it's ever gonna get clean.
Yeah, you should clean that table but never be finished cleaning that table.
Really reach, bro. Really reach.
Lay on it. Lay on the table.
Dude, get that bald guy's head. Get it. Get it.
I'll get it, I'll get it.
It's right on the side. I can see it.
I tried, I tried.
I see a stain, I got to clean it.
Murr, I want you to approach the guy in the white T -shirt.
I'm gonna have you shake his hand.
Hi, guys.
I got to shake your hand.
"Caught a peek in the urinal -- very impressive."
I'll tell you what.
I caught a peek at the urinals -- impressive.
It's true what they say.
The uniform lets you get away with so much.
Right.
Wiping those guys' table down, you would never get away with that.
That's why I've started to wear shirts everywhere that say my name on it.
Oh, that's you. You do that.
Is that why -- it makes your life better?
This is from the gas station.
Looks like it.
When we come back, we are going to show you a brand-new "Impractical Jokers" challenge.
And what happens when we tell this guy that he was on "Impractical Jokers"?
So, guys, I was poking around the vault, and guess what I found.
Love that vault!
I love that vault. I found a full challenge!
What?!
Not one turn or two turns -- all of our turns.
We never aired it?
No. We forgot to put it on.
I told you to remind us.
We should really go through that vault.
I feel like there's a lot of gold down there.
Just every time we go down there, we just party and party.
Oh, it's all parties in the vault, no work.
Where is the vault?!
It's downstairs.
So, guys, here you go
a challenge you've never seen before straight from the “jokers" vault.
We want to know your opinion,
which is why we're conducting a focus group.
Why are you so angry?
I'm focused!
On what, you ask? We have no idea.
Because the questions we're asking have been written by the other guys.
If you cannot ask every single question, you lose!
Focus!
How are you? Have a seat here.
So, have you ever done a focus group before?
Basically, we just get your opinions and thoughts on stuff and ask you a bunch of questions.
Let's do it.
So, how many hours of sleep do you average per night?
About seven or eight? All right.
Um... If Ray Ray comes around these parts, sniffing for a tip off.
You don't go squeal on a piggy, do you?
Snitches get stitches. I'll cut a bitch.
Would you like to trade "the time I shit my pants" stories?
I'll go first.
There was this time when I was on the bus and I didn't hold it in for a field trip.
We were going to the Turtle Back Zoo, and I [bleep] my pants.
You?
Uh
If I lost 20 pounds, would you dream of me?
No.
If I put on 20 pounds, would you dream of me?
What would I need to do for you to dream of me?
"Be black."
Good luck with that one, pal.
Go for it.
I've never been kissed. Would you do me the honors?
Congratulations, Joe.
Hello.
Hi. I'm James. How are you?
Hello, James.
What's your name?
Peter.
Peter, nice to meet you. Have a seat.
This guy is super serious about his opinions.
Shows up in a suit. He's here to play.
I'm going to ask you now a series of questions, OK?
All right.
So, I want you to answer "always," "sometimes," or "never."
OK. "I enjoy a cup of coffee."
Always.
At night?
Never.
"I take long showers."
Always.
With close relatives?
Never.
"I like to kiss."
Always.
Ass?
Never.
"I've been to a drive-through."
Sometimes.
Strip club?
Never.
Keep going.
Next question is...
They say...
What do they say, Murr?
What do they say? What do they say?
They say that "one in the hand is worth two in the bush."
How many -- how many hands do you prefer in your bush?
I have a bush?
That's what she said.
This guy's letting loose now, that's it.
What do you have to say to that piece of poop that just refuses to flush?
Objectively speaking.
OK, um, I'm trying to visualize.
"So, do me a favor -- pretend I'm a piece of poop."
So, let's role-play.
OK.
Let's say that I'm that piece of poop in question.
Flush.
Here we go, buddy.
Point to a place on my body that you think could be improved.
No hesitation!
You'd change my face?
What part of my body could be improved?
All right. Well, I'm just gonna ask you a few questions
and there's no wrong answers.
Here he goes.
You asked for it!
What's your technique when you go downtown?
Oh, I meant, like, train or bus or...
I see. You meant...
Rooty-toot-toot, you know?
Dropped a Rooty-toot-toot, you know?
So we just ask a series of questions kind of to track people's personal habits.
OK, James. Cool.
Just read it. Just read it.
Do you think I should finally give up on this game of hide and seek?
Now, Sal, yell, "I give up."
I give up.
Oh, my god!
And we just ask a series of questions
Just read it.just read it.
Do you think I should finally give up on this game of hide and seek?
Now, Sal, yell, "I give up."
I give up!
Oh, my god!
I win!
You know, she wins.
I still don't understand how that happened.
You put a child in a closet.
I was in that room for like 40 minutes.
We just put her in the corner with, like, an ice pop.
We're like, "Shh, honey."
I took that woman's advice. I grew the beard to work on this face.
You fixed it.
That was hurtful.
Well, I mean, I don't want to say anything, but I've been kissed twice since then.
Twice.
Both times in the vault, right?
Yeah! I love that vault!
Another really cool thing that happened during this focus group
is something we get asked a lot.
which is what happens when people find out they are on "Impractical Jokers".
We have one of those moments right now.
Let's take a look.
OK. Have you ever played organized sports?
Yes.
Yes. What kind?
Basketball, football, baseball.
This guy's really low-key.
He is. We got to go big on this guy.
Next question. Good luck.
These questions are getting me.
You ever watch "Impractical Jokers"?
What's that?
"Impractical Jokers."
Oh, he knows us!
At night, it's a cable show about these four guys
who challenge each other to say and do the most craziest things.
Really?
It is ridiculous.
He doesn't know it's him.
One time, they were in a bed store where they sell beds
and the guy was pretending like he was the salesman.
So he gets on the bed and was like, "get on the bed with him."
This is ikea. This is Sal's bit in ikea.
Got on the bed with him, and then he says, "OK, now spoon him."
"Spoon the guy?"
Get out of here. Did he do it? Did the guy spoon him?
Yeah, he did.
Oh, he sounds like the best one on the show.
They got balls -- all of them. They all of them got huge balls.
That's cool.
Yeah. You should watch it.
That's great. All right.
Well, Bob, that was actually -- you did great.
And actually the client's gonna come in just to say hello.
Let's see.
Hello, there.
You like that show "Impractical Jokers", huh?
I knew he was...
I'm saying, you cats got balls, man.
We were crying back there listening to you describe our show.
I'm gonna be honest with you, man.
There's not many TV shows I watch, but yours is a great [bleep] show.
Thank you. We appreciate it.
Well, we're glad you could be part of it.
Thank you so much.
How did that guy not know it was you he was talking to?
How have I not been invited to the vault?
Even if you knew where the vault was, you don't know the code to get in.
Don't even worry.
Thanks for watching "Impractical Jokers." we'll see you soon!
Guys, let's head down to the vault, shall we?
Yeah, all right! I get to go to the vault!
That's silly. That's just silly.
I'm not even gonna play along.
And that's why you never get to the vault.
That's why you never see it.
That's right.
They're under the table.