OK, Joe. Why'd you ask us here today?
It's our anniversary!
Three years of "Impractical Jokers."
That's right!
We shot our very first challenge at Chinatown Brasserie
eating food off people's plates on this very day.
So, to celebrate, I thought we'd have a party at the arcade...
...and then we'd spend time showing some unaired clips that no one has ever seen before.
That's a great idea.
Yes! They're unaired clips!
What?!
Yes! It's insanity!
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Can I take your order?
Sal, have a lot of soul here, buddy.
Be like a soulful R&B singer.
Yes, I'd like a No. 1 with cheese.
♪ You want that No. 1 with cheese
And make that a large.
♪ You want to make it a large with that cheese
Little more soul, buddy.
All right, I'm giving you soul!
A six-piece chicken.
♪ Six-piece chicken
That's it.
♪ Your total, one more time for the lord I said
♪ Your total is fifte-e-e-e-e-en ninety-one
Please drive around.
You definitely have soul, Buddy.
Yeah.
It's true. I do. I do have soul.
Sal, you're actually a reverend.
I am. I am a reverend.
That's right. Sal officiated Joe's wedding.
That's right.
Why wasn't my wedding ceremony so soulful?
Imagine I came out of your wedding and I was like...
♪ everybody
Help me out now.
♪ do you...
He's just got to find Beth.
Why the name Beth?
The only real answer is, why not?
Yes, that's it. That's the only answer.
Huh?
Oh, my god!
I'm gonna translate what you just said to that girl.
"Look, look! Is your name Beth?"
"Mother! Look, look! Mother, mother! Look, look!"
Adios.
Beth. There you are. You silly goose!
Beth.
What's your name?
Sarah.
What?
But what do people who know you and love you call you?
Sarah.
You couldn't help me out?
I'm sorry.
That's all right, Beth.
Sarah.
Sarah, Sarah. All right, thanks, Sarah.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
What is he doing?
What was that?
Did he just...?
Are you, uh...
Are you Beth, by any chance?
Yeah.
No!
Are you a Beth, for real? Are you a Beth?
That's amazing.
100% your name is Beth?
Yeah.
Can I see that note?
What are you doing?
"Hi. I'm playing a game, and I have to find a person named Beth.
Can you say your name is Beth when I ask? Please and thanks, Sal."
You're a cheating s.o.b.
Your name is not Beth.
Shame on you for joining in on his shenanigans.
You can't get past us, buddy. There's cameras everywhere.
Honestly, how dare you, though, come down on me for cheating.
You cheat all the time.
Don't try and swap this.
We're dealing with you right now.
My favorite part of the whole thing is -- OK, you cheated
But then these two start yelling at the girl...
Pointing at her!
You're like, "You should be ashamed of yourself!"
I was like, "You son of a bitch! What are you --"
She went home and cried.
Let's take a look at Sal's next clip.
One of the great things about the Borgata Hotel
is that they are pet-friendly.
So Q decided to bring...
I brought Benjamin to work tonight, my cat.
All right, come on in.
All right. Just let them in.
Help them into the bed.
You can set the bags down here.
Whose shirt?
I'm not sure.
Oh. Oh, what's that?
Is that your shirt, buddy?
Check the closet and see if there's anything in the closet.
I bet you in the closet in the bathroom, there might be some more of your stuff.
Here we go.
Oh, not again, not again! I hate this [bleep] thing! I hate this thing!
Stop it!
People ask me why I run.
And the answer is simple -- it's just this innate thing
If something's chasing you, you don't want it to get you.
Next time it happens, bud, because you know we'll do it again
just haul off and punch it in the head, and then be like, "Is that funny?!"
That'll be the end of it.
"Who's laughing now, kitty-cat?!"
Now it's the moment you've all been waiting for --
James Murray clip.
Murr, this guy in the red, I'm worried about his mouth.
Yeah, you don't want him to burn his tongue.
What're we gonna do, fellas? He's drinking hot coffee.
Yeah.
Needs to cool down. You got to cool it down.
What do you want me to do?
I'm saying blow on this guy's coffee.
Oh, is that too hot for you, sir?
Is that very hot?
We made a brand-new pot, so apologetic...
Pastrami Reuben.
Blow it as he's putting it in his mouth.
Come on.
Open up for a second.
You see that guy sitting across from the guy in the suit?
Yeah.
Murr, I want you to leer at him.
Oh, my god!
He leers better than Murr.
Look! It's a stare-down!
Don't break! Don't you break!
Oh, my god.
I was sweating.
That was intense, buddy.
No, I liked that the guy was just waiting for him to lose to laugh it off, too.
That guy, he looked like he woke up this morning ready for a leer-off.
He's a professional.
It actually looked like you two were related somehow.
Alright, let's take a look at another Murr clip.
Once again, the Murr man finds himself in a position he would never be in.
Just trying to make an honest living.
Murr, Murr, Murr! Go up to him right now.
In a very secretive way, "You got the full service, right?"
Yeah, you got the full service, right?
Yes.
"Where do you want to do this?"
All right, where do you wanna do this?
What?
So where do you wanna do this?
What are you talking about?
That means hands-free drying.
So you just put the rag in front of your pants here.
You're gonna hump this car into drydom.
Tuck it right in.
OK, now go ahead, bud.
There you go, Murr. Hands behind your head.
There you go, there you go!
This guy's taking a picture of him!
They're both taking pictures of Murray!
Murr, on a scale of 1 to 10, how much of an idiot do you feel like right now?
I feel like a jackass.
I want to know why that video hasn't wound up on Youtube yet.
You think you know every video on Youtube?
How often do you Internet search "James Murray humping"?
You have alerts set up. Don't lie.
There's a whole Youtube channel devoted to it.
Let's take a look at another clip that Murr knows is not on the Internet.
Hello.
Sayo-- uh, ba-- banzai.
"Banzai."
So, Murr, start banging around the spatulas.
Threaten someone with the knife very subtly.
Look at this guy. Look at this guy.
He's eyeballing.
He's already pissed. Murray hasn't even said anything.
All right, Murr, just want you to throw a full squash at the guy in white.
Throw one and go, "Yummy!"
Yummy!
Murr, be the most depressed Hibachi chef.
"Bank foreclosed on my studio apartment."
The bank foreclosed on my studio apartment.
"Sleeping on my friend's futon."
Been sleeping on my friend's futon lately.
"I got rear-ended in traffic the other day."
I got rear-ended in traffic the other day.
"Thank god I wasn't in my car."
Thank god... Thank god I wasn't in my car.
You don't cook at all.
No, no, no.
You don't even know how to make toast.
No, no. I tried to cook for my parents the other day.
How'd that go?
I ordered out.
Hey, now it's time to look at some of Joe's clips.
Joe's not a great dancer, but he dances with crazy passion and conviction.
Hey. How's it going?
It's 99% conviction, 1% skill with him.
Has everybody here taken a hip-hop class before?
Joe, get the tall guy and demand that he serve you.
So, we're gonna do an introduction to serving here.
A serve is basically like a dance battle.
So, the thing, you know, where people take turns dancing and doing their best moves
And then one person looks...at them as they do their moves, and then they go.
Sir, step forward. I'll show you what I mean.
Stand there with your arms folded.
So, you know, you can start over here, and I'm like, I come up, I size you up.
This is serving.
I'm like, "all right." I might give you a nickname -- I might say "too tall."
Here we go. Boom! And I drop it on you.
Like that, right? And step it out.
And now you serve.
Walk around me.
Right? There he is.
Right? And now you just come up and do a little --
See? I didn't even know what happened.
That was great. Good. Good.
That was like a karate move.
You just got served!
All right, everybody, bop out. Relax.
Just feel the music.
"OK, I just want to talk about the night my wife died for a second."
So, I'm just gonna talk to you real quick about the, uh...
The... The night my wife died.
So, we are out dancing, having a good time.
That night, god served my wife.
Why don't you just dance out of the room without saying a word?
That's it, buddy.
Right out of the room.
Dance out of the room!
Don't say a word to them. Just open the door...
That was insane -- "god served my wife."
That room got so weird so fast.
If you notice, everyone's blurred in that room.
When we come back, we're gonna show you some more never-before-seen clips from IJ
Hey, guys, how are you doing?
I'm out here doing some volunteer-squad stuff in New York city, right?
Yeah.
So, you sign up to be a volunteer.
This is the Pal-paca Society.
It's people who are gonna be friends with alpacas.
You know alpacas, the big thing with the neck and it's hairy?
You know it looks like sort of fake emu.
So what we do at the Pal-paca Society is
we rescue alpacas that have been abandoned by their alpaca owners.
Do you guys crochet?
No.
No? 'Cause we were looking for Pal-paca Blankets.
We call them Pal-blankets.
So, uh, do you guys do anything with Pal-paca weaving?
No.
No? Are you good on the Internet?
No? What the [bleep] do you do?
I'm not sure you can help anyone at this point.
Just doing Portuguese mainly.
You speak Portuguese.
Obrigado, right? You know what I'm saying.
Don't you know a Portuguese love song?
Um, I know a Portuguese love song.
Let's go.
♪ vinyado, vinyado, vinyado
♪ do you know...?
You don't know that one?
It was all the rage last year.
What's your name?
Julia.
Julia. All right.
Julia's gonna get her volunteer on.
Ba-boom! Just do it. Don't even think about it.
He's getting them. He's getting them.
Yeah, absolutely. Pal-paca Society.
My thing is, you're trying to get them to volunteer
and you literally asked the girl what the [bleep] she does.
But she did nothing. She had no discernible skills in life.
Her job was to walk around the park in a bra.
That's her job.
Let's take a look at another Joe's clip.
Hi. Dollar hot dogs. Yeah?
What would you like?
Ketchup, mustard, relish.
Gotcha. OK.
"Holy molasses! I got to [bleep]"
I just realized something.
Holy molasses.
I gots to [bleep]
You're out here all day, slinging dogs...
I got a footer coming out.
Relish or no?
Yeah.
Oh, this relish is making me think...
"And it's between the buns."
And it's between the buns.
So, this is gonna...
In a minute, there's gonna be something like this going on.
Thanks.
Why are you guys obsessed with me talking about [bleep]?
Because you [bleep] all the time.
Well, so do humans! I'm human.
All right, let's take a look at some never-before-seen clips of Q.
Thanks, everybody, for coming.
Q knows nothing of fashion.
He always looks like a disheveled crazy person.
All right. Why don't we get the show started, huh?
And so it begins.
"This biotch gots a hat on!"
This biotch gots a hat on.
And I feel it speaks for itself.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
That biotch did, in fact, have a hat.
All right. Uh, let's -- let's see the next model.
This is the, uh...
He has no idea what to say.
There's nothing to say.
This -- there's no way to explain that.
This, uh -- uh, I like to call it sickly chic.
Easy access if he's got to use the bedpan.
You got the -- They went ahead with the black eyes, too, so you really look sick.
You're the designer!
You're surprised he went with the black eyes.
Uh, all right. Well, uh, next model.
Oh, my god.
Yep. Yeah, that's right.
There, we got it. That's a sexy homicidal maniac.
Oh, doesn't she look pretty?
Yeah, I think you guys can see this for Halloween next year, right?
Yeah.
OK. All right, uh, next model.
It's just a delivery guy.
He doesn't know what to say!
I think that he just -- I think he was actually just delivering some food.
That was so much fun.
I remember being backstage and all those costumes were running around.
It was like an episode of "The Muppet Show."
It was crazy.
Now let's take another look at a never-before-seen clip of Q.
Excuse me. Sir? Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you. I'm in a bit of a tight spot.
I -- I, uh -- I have to call... Black Raphael.
You know, the guy Black Raphael?
I got to let him know, uh... Rock Hudson died.
And it's kind of an emergency because he's been waiting for that day.
And I left my phone...
Oh, god.
I, uh -- I left my phone, uh...
I left my -- I left my phone up your ass and to the left, I guess.
Can I borrow yours to make a phone call?
Real quick -- to Black Raphael.
He's walking around think Liberace's still alive!
Rock Hudson, not Liberace!
Oh, Rock Hudson's dead.
Liberace?
They're both dead, you know
Flamboyant gentlemen.
I consider one of my weaknesses is my body.
And I look at a man who's chiseled, and I'm like -- I'm a little bit jealous.
Murr, when you looked at that guy's head of hair...
Let's take a look at the next clip.
Q, I want you to take your boots off and put them in someone's cart.
Without them knowing.
There you go.
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
You got them.
She put her stuff right next to your boots and didn't notice them.
Oh, her husband's there, too,
He's pointing it out to her.
Q, walk to her right now and be like, "all right, wise guy!"
All right, wise guys.
Come on. Stop stealing my boots.
That's the third time today.
Watch your boots around these two.
Why don't you just lay down on the floor right here?
That's it.
He's not dead. Just taking a facedown nap.
Oh, my god.
You look dead. You look like a chalk outline.
This is disgusting.
People are staring.
Roll over on your back, like you were just sleeping.
All good here. Just chillin'.
That's all it takes -- the thumbs up.
You're all good.
You can really see the devolution of me throughout this episode.
I was kind of clean-cut and, you know, happy in the beginning.
And towards the end, I just look like I'm homeless.
I think you guys are right about me.
Self-fulfilling prophecy.
I didn't see it before, but you guys kept calling me homeless, and now I look homeless.
Welcome to the end of this episode of "Impractical Jokers".
Well, guys, we did it. There it is -- three years of fun.
Congratulations, guys.
And thank you to everybody at home who have supported us the entire time.
We could not have done it without you.
And we're looking forward to the next 300 years.
That's right.
What?
Well, I'll be dead in two.
Cheers, everyone!
Cheers!