Oh, America, what's up? You look great.
Sometimes on our show
There's just too much delicious goodness to squeeze into an episode.
All of us have tons of crazy moments like that that you've never seen.
So I came up with a brilliant idea
To take those moments and put them in one episode.
Yes, so, please, America. Send him "thanank you" letters,
Because you're about to see all of our un-aired bonus footage.
Let's get YOLO!
What's YOLO?
You only live once!
—Let's get you only live once?  —Yeah.
Let's get you only live once and watch those clips right now.
That makes sense to you. To you, that makes sense.
So, here's a bit of trivia for youse.
Before we film a challenge, we decide who goes first by yelling "not it."
Not it. Not it. Not it.
You're up first.
You lose, which means you're up first, which means you're in for a treat.
Footage of Sally boy over here working as a receptionist
Sign in, I need to ask you a couple questions real quick.
Pick up the phone.
Hey, Maurice, could you find the -- yes.
I couldn't find the files from earlier.
Put your finger up. Put your finger up to her.
Now, I'll be right with you. Just one second.
Now, just leave it there, Sal.
(Talking on the phone...)
Move that finger closer to her. Get it closer to her.
(Still talking on the phone...)
Just one second, please.
(Continuing talking on the phone...)
Get that finger closer to her. Closer! Closer!
(Almost done...)
OK. Thank you.
I'm sorry. I'll be right with you.
What would you do if someone went like that to you?
Would you know it was a joke, or would you get mad, or what would you do?
I would lick or kiss the finger.
I wish you wouldn't say things like that.
OK, Sal, so give this woman a pedicure.
He's looking at the other people... to see how they give a pedicure.
How long have you been in New York?
Well...
Everything she says
Try to repeat exactly what she's saying as she says it.
How long have you been up in this neighborhood?
Just, um, since June.
It's ... European.
it's ... European.
Gently shush her when she talks.
How long's your, uh, commute on the subway?
—Half an hour.  —Shh.
—If I get the con--  —Shh.
You said you were in what part of Brooklyn?
—Uh...  —Shh.
—It's expensive --  —Shh.
Open-mouth sneeze on her foot.
Oh, my god. That would be amazing if he does that.
He's hiding! He's hiding!
You guys were merciless with me on that one.
—If you were getting a pedicure --  —Shh.
Hi, how are you?
Good. How are you?
Good.
You're just picking up or --
You need to try them on.
Get ready to compliment those pants, Sal.
Those are nice pants!
Do it. Do it.
Hey, Laura, those are nice pants!
Hey, Laura. Those are nice pants!
Oh, another pair of pants.
Oh, those are nice, too!
Laura... Those are nice pants, too.
I like those better than the other ones.
Oh, my god! Those are my favorite pants!  Laura!
Oh, my god! Laura! Those are my favorite!
You see Laura's pants?!
You sound like, uh, the Kool-aid guy.
Oh, yeah!
All right. Enough is enough with me.
But stick around, because we have clips from Murr coming up next.
Wow! It's me!
You know, some people don't realize this, but I'm actually a mastermind.
The mastermind with the fool-proof plan.
Yeah, that never works.
Sometimes it works.
No, no, no. Zero. Exactly zero times it works.
There was one time.
Never. Never.
All right. Let's take a look at the master at work.
James. Nice to meet you.
How long have you been a member of the gym?
He's been going to this gym for 20 years?!
What is Murray gonna tell him?
Do you, uh, aerobic, as well?
You've never done aerobic exercise a day in your life?
Jumping jacks. Right now.
Let's do some cardio, OK? Do it!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
Let's do it a bit faster.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Want to build up a sweat.
You got to build up a sweat. That's it.
Stop. Stop suddenly.
Good. Take it slow. Take it slow. Take it slow.
Murr, jumping jacks! Jumping jacks!
Come on. Faster. Faster.
Go in circles.
Circle it up.
That's it. Right here. I'm right here.
I'm right here.
When you get caught doing the same routine, you're not making any progress.
You have to keep the body guessing between aerobic...
Murr! Jumping jacks!
...and anaerobic workout.
Spin, spin, spin.
Go free form. Free form. Spin around. Spin around.
This guy's just following him.
That's it.
And now in my face.
Let's do it. Let's do it together.
That's it. That's it. Right here.
You are a man!
Why'd you stop, bro?
I thought you were stopping.
If any of us were on the floor, we would have been dead.
It would have been a totally different joke.
It would have been about killing one of us.
"Do a jumping jack. Go. Joe? Wake up. Joe?"
I got to tell you, though. You look great in a headband.
That headband did a great job keeping my forehead out of my eyes.
Do you play?
No.
No? You're doing pretty good.
Ask her what her name is.
I'm James, by the way.
Brandi, nice to meet you.
Where you from?
Oh, is that right?
"Brandi, I have to tell you something."
I have to tell you something, by the way.
"I am an artist."
I am an artist.
"I wrote a song about you in my head right now."
And I wrote a song about you in my head right now.
"And I'm gonna play it for you right now, on this piano."
"Everything. I have everything."
Apparently, I've got everything.
Brandi.
♪ Brandi from Guam
♪ you are the bomb
"♪ my face makes you vom"
♪ my face makes you vom
♪ Brandi is so from Guam
♪ Brandi from Guam
"♪ I'm hairy like King Kong"
♪ I'm hairy like King Kong
"♪ can I get some?"
♪ can I get some?
♪ oh, Brandi
? Brandi from Guam left me like my mom
If I had a nickel for every woman that's run that fast from me...
Then got away.
Got away changes that figure drastically.
He gets most of them before they hit the highway.
We're all in luck
Because we have more never-before-seen clips of Murr playing a podiatrist.
Getting down with the feetsies.
Let's take a look.
Ok. So, now, which leg is hurting more?
Fix the back of the chair. It wasn't fixed for her.
It's my feet...
Is this not that comfortable? Let me tilt this back up for you, OK?
Oop. Sorry.
Oh, do it back and forth and up and down.
Keep moving her up and down. Keep moving her up and down.
There we go. Is that better?
OK, Murr, say, "All right, so with the feet..."
With the feet...
"You know what? Let me adjust this chair."
You know what? Let me adjust the chair.
Keep doing it!
—Is that better?  —Yeah, it's good.
—A little more comfortable?  —Yeah.
Let's take a look.
Murr, "we're just gonna check out this foot right here."
I'm just gonna check this foot out real quick, OK?
Now just stand up, buddy. Pop right up. Stand up.
And now swing your leg over it so your ass is facing her.
Put her leg through your legs.
The foot, uh -- the right foot, do you feel any pressure?
You almost got it, bud.
Do you feel any pressure with the right foot over here at all?
She went to grab his ass!
I'm gonna get the doctor real quick on this.
—She didn't know anyone was watching her.  —Right.
So, that was just all for her.
What's odd, though, is that I never thought I had a juicy buttocks.
Please don't -- please don't say things like that.
Well, I don't have a squeezable buttocks.
My butt is kind of bony and not squeezable and enjoyable.
After we come back from the break, we'll see some clips about Q.
Welcome back to "Impractical Jokers."
We are taking a look, tonight, at never-before-seen moments.
And right now, it is Q's turn.
Q, how do you do it, buddy?
How do I do what?
Just stumble your way through every day of your life?
You know, it's a skill.
No matter what time of day it is, you always seem cranky, tired, and disoriented.
That's because you guys set out to make me look that way.
I feel this new footage is gonna position me in a new light.
So, let's take a look at some never-before-seen, un-aired Q moments.
We are from Sensitivity Coaches, Incorporated.
We've been hired to come speak with you today
On sensitivity in the workplace.
Please make sure to remain professional.
These are your clients, your co-workers.
They are not your friends, and nicknames --
—To make them appropriate.  —Correct.
That was probably actually the most racist music.
Why did we put that in?
It came preloaded.
Inappropriate nicknames would be, uh...
Kung Fu Lou.
Unless -- unless his name is Lou...
And he happens to do Kung Fu.
Then that's just respect.
Inappropriate nicknames for this gentleman in the office.
Black-aroni & cheese.
You guys aren't gonna like if somebody's like "yo, you seen black-aroni & cheese?"
Right?
You mean, Trevor?
Now... OK... A kid in a wheelchair.
Uh, don't call the kid in the wheelchair "wheels."
"What's up, wheels?"
You actually tackled Joe in slow motion at the end.
Sometimes I can't take it, man. I just can't take it.
But your body looks like a puppet.
You know, when you release --
Like a marionette?
Oh, my god! You do that really well.
All right. So, there's still more of Q.
Let's take a look at another never-seen-before clip.
It's decision time.
Pick your poison!
Catch someone in a net.
Like a fishing net. Net us a person.
Oh, and throw a water balloon at someone.
They're both good choices. I know it's like
"Which one? They're both so good."
I hate the three of you.
I'm gonna catch someone in a net.
You're gonna try.
I'm immediately regretting my choice now that I'm holding this giant net in my hand.
—Looks completely natural.  —Yes.
He's got to net them, right, like down to here?
You got to catch someone. They're getting away.
I know. You think this is easy?
Here we go. This guy right here.
—Yeah, this guy to the right. Yep?  —Yep.
The element of surprise.
Hey, what's going on, man? How you doing?
You look like a catch is what I'm saying, huh?
So, you are trying, man.
You're trying, but you are not netting anyone.
You're not catching somebody.
The card specifically says --
I know. I know what it says. I know what it says!
That guy, that guy.
I -- please. That's my favorite net.
You can keep it. You can have it.
Oh, my god.
Technically, I caught him before he -- he...
You know what? Let me tell you something about that guy.
Is he actually turned out to be really, really nice after he found out it was a joke.
When he thought he was getting caught in a net, he wasn't happy about it.
He thought I was a crazy jerk.
Slap yourself.
We all want to do it from here, so we figure we'd put you in charge.
And don't make it a love tap. Make it a hefty slap.
Use that meat hook you got.
All right, purp.
'Sup, purps. What's going on?
Hi.
Come here often?
Um...
Now.
Is there any places around her kind of nice that I should see?
There's a lot.
There's a lot? Give me -- just give me a favor.
Brother Jimmy's
Now.
What else?
She thinks this is hitting on her.
He's hitting on her or hitting himself?
He's hitting on him.
I'm not sure.
You're not sure?
No.
—Now.  —Now.
Deuce. We dropped the deuce on him.
All right. I'm gonna go.
Yeah, you go.
I would appreciate it if you would go.
"But let me tell you one more thing before you go."
Oh, just one more thing before you go.
Now.
Bye!
You have the meatiest of hooks.
I do.
So, that was coming in -- you were coming in with some velocity.
Giant ham hands.
—Look at the difference in your hands.  —You could crush his skull.
I feel like I'm holding hands with a girlfriend.
When we come back from break,
We're gonna take a look at some of Joe's never-before-seen moments.
Your turn!
Joe's approach can be summed up in one word -- loud.
Everybody has a strategy, mine is just louder, that's all.
Is that a strategy or a way of life?
'Cause I've met your family, and you're all louder than the next.
People that marry into your family -- like, if they're not loud
The day after the wedding,
They're sitting there going like this, cracking jokes...
You want to be heard. You want to be heard.
On that note, let's take a look at some brand-new clips from Joe!
Joe, you see this guy in the blue bathing suit?
Stand right over him until he wakes up and notices.
Oh, this is tough.
You're gonna get him punched, man.
In the balls. In the balls.
Doing all right? Everything's OK here?
Are you doing OK?
Yeah, I'm good.
We've got the rip tide and everything. You did all right?
—Yeah, I'm all right.  —OK, good.
Just checking in with everybody, making sure everybody's doing OK on the beach.
Thanks, bud.
Yeah, he's OK.
All right, Joey. This guy in the yellow shorts.
I'm trying to work out the angle.
He's got his, like, leg crossed with like a weird arm.
And it's such a weird position.
You doing ok? Everything OK?
Everything OK with the rip tide?
Earlier, in the water, you were OK?
—Good.  —It's all good.
And you're good, too?
Earlier, you were in the water earlier?
Oh, no. You were only in the beach? Oh, OK.
Oh, an hour ago?
No, no. I thought -- sorry.
I thought that it was earlier when you were in the water.
I didn't know if that was you.
You -- you haven't been...
'Cause they had called it in earlier somebody ...
"Can you move, please?"
Oh, OK. Then it wasn't you.
I was looking for the other guy, then.
It wasn't -- no. It wasn't him.
That was one of the rare moments that the cops have been called on us.
What was his complaint to the police?
"Excuse me, there's a beach-patrol guy
With his crotch too close to my sleeping body."
But wait. There's more Joe footage to come.
Let's take a look at him working at the White Castle drive-through.
Joe, hand her everything individually.
Napkins... condiments, straws, salt...
One at a time.
Everything à la carte.
OK. There's your large sweet tea.
Here's a straw for your drink.
There's a napkin.
There's your sack of onion rings.
And that's the bag for the sack of onion rings.
First cheeseburger.
Bag for the first cheeseburger.
Second cheeseburger.
Ketchup for the second cheeseburger.
Here's the honey mustard
Here's the honey mustard.
Here's a honey mustard.
There's honey mustard.
Honey mustard. Honey mustard.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Oh, my god. My cheeks hurt right now.
Like Copperfield -- one at at time.
It was all in The Prestige. Here you go.
My favorite's when you just started throwing [bleep] into the car.
Now let's take a look at some never-before-seen footage
Of Joe working as a receptionist.
Here you go. Have a seat right there.
Doing all right, Glen?
Good, man.
Joe, while you're talking to him, why don't you get up and adjust yourself?
They have a new piano coming out that works with bluetooth.
It works with bluetooth.
Bluetooth technology -- it plays the melody in your ear.
Scratch your ass with the desk.
Now, you find -- you like T-Mobile?
I had AT&T for a while, and I switched over to the other company.
They gave the better plan -- unlimited minutes.
Get that desk in your ass crack.
What kind of data plan do you got?
This guy is unflappable.
—I bet he's a poker champ.  —Yeah, yeah.
Unlimited minutes?
While you're talking to him, can you go sit on his lap?
No, you don't want a new one?
Yeah. I don't either.
I mean, I'm good with it.
When is, uh -- when's your contract up?
Two years.
He's not making any face!
That's amazing, man. That's absolutely amazing.
What the [bleep]
Oh, my god.
So, that's why I switched to Verizon.
What was that guy thinking?
He didn't break for a moment.
That guy -- I've spent more time thinking about that guy
Because what has he seen?
He's been through some stuff.
I had a better conversation with him while I was scratching my ass
Than I've ever had with him.
Well, that was fun.
—That was great.  —That was something.
It was a great time.
Thank you very much for joining us on these un-aired clips of "Impractical Jokers."
So, say goodnight, Sal.
Goodnight, Sal!