Coming up, why is Q getting creamed?
What has Joe playing games?
Guess who.
And tonight's big loser faces an Olympic-sized punishment.
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
We are here at fairway supermarket, shopping with the good people of Brooklyn.
While browsing the aisles, we're going to do and say what the other guys tell us.
And if you refuse, you lose.
Hey, Joe.
Where is Joe?
Here he comes.
Man, he's in a rush.
Joe, shop like your life depends on it.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Where the [bleep] they put the macaroni?
There's other pastas.
Where the [bleep] fusilli?
Oh, look at him.
Where's the RigaTones?
Where's the pappardelle?
How you feeling, pal?
Joe, this aisle's under your surveillance.
Report back to us what you find.
I got eyes on the woman in the scarf.
Subject has a gallon of milk in hand.
Seems like this couple might be, uh, suspicious.
He's having a meeting right behind me.
The female subject has disengaged. The male subject's on the move.
Subject has blue pants.
I've been made. She's on the move. She's on the move.
Stop this guy.
Show him the mini cucumbers.
Let me ask you something.
These are mini cucumbers.
Ask him how many he could fit.
Uh... All right, bud, have a good day.
Here he comes. Man on a mission.
Sal be shoppin'!
Sal, on 3, I want you to whip your cart to the right.
Ready? 1, 2, 3!
I was getting butter.
So much dairy.
See this guy with the headphones in?
Get his attention.
Now wave at him.
That's it.
I'm sorry?
He was so freaked out.
Sal, push into this woman's cart. Hijack it.
Keep going, keep going.
Sal, the kid -- hijack his cart.
The father
He has no idea what happened!
Tell this kid to keep quiet, Sal.
Here he is, just picking up some groceries.
I'm glad you wore a superhero shirt, buddy.
Hey, Q, what is interesting is your arch-nemesis right here in this Fairway.
There he is.
Well, well, well, we meet again.
Am I?
"Oh, I don't know. A supervillain!"
A supervillain!
Oh, it's a stand-off.
Nobody said, "eat whipped cream."
Q, when people leave their cart, put a dollop of whipped cream on the handlebar.
Put some whipped cream all over your face.
By the way, bud, whipped cream's not a good look.
He just put his hands in it!
Turn around, turn around, turn around!
Put a dollop of whipped cream on the handlebar.
Put some whipped cream all over your face.
He just put his hands in it!
Turn around, turn around, turn around!
Wasn't me.
Get this woman right here. "Excuse me."
Excuse me.
"My priest says I like zucchini too much."
My priest says I like zucchini too much.
Point to that cart and ask them where they got that.
I'm sorry. Where did you get that from? What aisle was that in?
"No, the kid."
Uh, the kid.
I can't make any of my own -- I'm barren.
So I thought I'd come to the supermarket. Maybe they had some.
A woman is barren, you idiot.
Men are sterile. Women are barren, is it?
Sorry. I'm sterile.
Murr.
Yo.
Be careful. These carts are slippery. They get out of control.
Just send your cart flying down the aisle and tell everyone to look out. Lose control of it.
Oh, like a runaway cart?
It's a runaway cart!
It got right out of my hands. I'm so sorry.
She jumped out of her shoes.
This woman -- stop her.
Can I stop you for one sec?
What's up?
"I have to tell you..."
I have to tell you...
"...my wife and I have a deal."
...my wife and I have this deal.
"We can sleep with anybody that we meet at the supermarket."
We can sleep with anybody we meet at the supermarket.
Seriously?
Yes.
"So, hi, I'm James."
I'm James.
What's up? I'm Hailey.
Hailey, nice to meet you.
That's a really cool rule.
I mean, not me.
Joe couldn't produce a win, so he's first up on the loser board.
Today, we're approaching park-goers with the mystery bag.
What's in it?
Something completely bizarre that's been packed by the other guys.
The goal is to convince stranger to keep the item.
If you can't get them to keep the item, you lose.
The mystery bag!
Enough!
Who's going to stop for me when I approach them
and say, "Excuse me. I want to give you what's in this bag"?
That's not our problem, buddy. It's your problem.
Here you go, Sal -- behind you. How about this lady?
Excuse me.
I'm giving this away today, and it's a great find.
If you want it, I just...
There it is. It's grandma oil.
This is, uh... It's 80 years' worth of oil.
Think about the things you use oil for every day.
And now think about if you had an unlimited supply of it.
It's limited. There's one jar.
Well, actually, it is a limited supply, but the opportunity with it is unlimited
If you really try hard.
You could do anything with this, right?
You could reapply.
What, to your own grandmother?
Your own grandma's drying out.
You can put it to get a tan. Ironically, takes out wrinkles.
Tastes good on a salad.
Do you know how hard it is to gather oil from your grandmother every day? It's hard.
Yeah, because she doesn't always want to do it. She's fickle.
When they get up there in age, they want to do it less and less.
In her 60s, my grandmother was giving the oil away.
She's 80 now -- I got to wring it out of her in her sleep.
"Shut up, grandma!"
So, if you would like this grandma oil, this is yours to keep, from me to you.
Why don't you take the grandma oil?
All right, thank you.
Bye.
Big fail, bro.
No dice, buddy. No one's ever gonna take grandma oil. This is [bleep]
Mystery bag, huh?
I can't help but feel that you have not taken the mystery bag seriously this entire time.
The bag of mystery?
I think you're a nonbeliever, and we're about to make you believe.
Yeah, yeah.
Who asks a man holding a duffel bag to take a family photo?
Here we go.
There you go.
Oh, let me talk to you one second.
Go ahead, kids. Go ahead.
I don't need what I got in this bag here, so it's for free.
I just didn't know if you wanted it.
But, uh, this is -- oh.
Um... This may come in handy for you specifically.
Based on your history, I think --
You sure you're all right?
Because you seem to be shooting straight every time. You got a huge family.
You seem to be good at what you do, and I was wondering if you wanted to stop it.
With the present situation, you don't want any more of those things run around.
Are you serious? I wonder what's in the bag.
It's a mystery bag, bro.
It could be anything.
I don't think you understand the definition of the word "mystery."
It could be a sack of bananas.
You know, there could be a puppy in there.
Who carries an i.v. stand around with them?
What are you talking about?
Did you peek?
You jerks.
Hey, guys, I'm trying to give this away.
It's free. I don't want any money for it.
But let me show you what it is, in case you haven't figured it out yet.
It's a working i.v. stand. Now -- oh [bleep]
That's what we did!
Hold on. Hear me out. This is universal blood.
This is type o-negative. You can use it for anyone or anything.
You never know in a pinch.
It fell apart on me.
It's a broken i.v. stand.
Just give me a thumbs-down now.
There's no way I'm giving this to anyone.
Hey, okay, no problem. Enh!
This is ridiculous.
All right, Q, there's your mystery bag, buddy.
This smells...
Does it smell of mystery?
It just smells like a rotting carcass.
It's a mystery bag.
Nobody's gonna want to come near me.
All I'm telling you is, it's pretty hot out.
I would get rid of what's in there right away.
You're really pretty. You want to know what's in my bag here?
What about you, hotshot? You want to know what's in the bag?
Yo, stripes, what's up?
Mystery bag.
Hi. How you doing?
Good. How are you?
Good. I have something -- I'm not selling anything.
I have something that I'm absolutely...
Oh, you're broke?
Good. You're gonna love this. 'Cause you can just have this.
It's, uh... Oh, my good god.
I have something -- I'm not selling anything.
I have something that I'm absolutely...
Oh, you're broke?
Good. You're gonna love this. 'Cause you can just have this.
It's, uh... Oh, my good god.
Do you like seafood?
I saw it swimming around. It doesn't smell.
Oh, my god!
Disgusting!
I caught this in that fountain over there.
Do you want it?
She's running like the terminator from "Terminator II."
She's just like, "aah!"
I know you love sushi. You want some?
You want it? I'm giving it away.
Here you go, man.
I know. It's nuts. Take it.
If he takes that, I'm gonna punch you in the face, so be prepared.
Go ahead and take that.
There you go. Sweet.
Oh, my god! He gave him the fish!
What?
He's got to walk away with it.
Is he walking away with it?
He's walking away with it.
Sal, Joe, and Murr couldn't find any takers, so they're up on the loser board.
Today, we're in the mall, playing food-court roulette.
We'll each be given a task that we'll have to do to one of these people.
The catch is, we don't know which one.
And we'll have to keep doing it until we find the person the other guys have secretly chosen.
If you can't find the person that the other guys picked, you lose.
Cling clang!
It's Joe and Murr in a joker vs. Joker challenge.
Guys, how about this guy right here?
Yes.
Old guy, green hat.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ready, Joe?
Yep.
We have the chosen one.
All right, what are we doing?
Go up to people from behind, cover their eyes, and ask them "guess who."
I like the way that started. I didn't like the finish.
What, go up behind people? That's the part you like?
Well, there's somebody that might be of interest.
You think you know who we chose?
It might be this cat right here-ski.
Joe, I think you to browse a little more.
And that's confirmed my suspicions.
Buddy, I don't want to browbeat you about this, but you want to step this up?
Guess who.
Huh? Is that it?
Nope.
No, all right.
Pleased to meet you, bud. Joe.
He was just like annoyed.
Oh, there's just so many people eating.
Look at this, look at this.
This is the guy. The guy's leaving!
Joe, if the person leaves the food court before you find them, you lose.
Oh, this old son of a bitch?
He's out! He's out of the food court! He's out of the food court!
Oh, god!
It's over.
How did an old man outrun me?
So we're picking this guy right here with the two chicks.
It's not the chicks.
It's the guy.
All right, Murr, here's what you got to do, my friend.
You're gonna shoot an obvious evil look in their face.
Oh, this look?
Right, that's it.
All right, Murr, you ready?
I'm going in.
Here he goes.
I think it's this guy.
Ehh! Nice try.
This is great. He's gonna have a hundred enemies.
I think it's this woman in pink right here, the mother.
Here goes nothing.
Enh! Wrong one, buddy.
Nice try. Keep it moving.
You better hurry up, buddy. If they leave the food court, you lose.
Scandinavian woman.
The chicken and broccoli is good, ma'am?
Not her.
Nope. Wrong fella.
I got it. It's the two blondes sitting at the table behind me here.
The two blondes sitting right there?
Uh-huh.
Not the one guy we picked, who's sitting with them.
Uh, there's a table with a couple folks with luggage. I'm right by them.
Yeah, right there.
Look at his face!
Enh!
Good look. Wrong person.
I give up. This is crazy.
Who is it?
It's the guy right in front of you!
This guy?
Yeah!
I did the two blondes that he was with. I didn't -- oh!
Damn it.
Looks like Joe and Murr chose poorly, but only Joe is tonight's big loser.
If there's one thing Joe is, it's a loser.
One thing he's not is flexible, strong, agile, nimble, athletic.
Okay, I get it.
He's not a gymnast.
Today, you're gonna be playing one on TV.
We're gonna throw you in the mix with a bunch of actual experienced gymnasts.
And you have to show them how to do it better.
How to do what better?
Everything.
What's our insurance plan? Because I'm gonna get [bleep] up.
Look at him. Look --
It looks like you have a medicine ball in your shirt.
Holy [bleep]
Joe, the little girl...
You can do better.
I know you're young, but I could do it better.
So when you see the good stuff, I want you to take that in.
Oh my god!
Even if you fall, you want to use the momentum to keep going.
We came up with a punishment that might kill Joe Gatto.
So, I'm gonna send you over to the vault.
You can do better than them.
I'm gonna kill myself.
Watch and learn.
I saw what you did last time.
I'm just gonna show you a different way to stick the landing.
Okay.
I could do it better.
Take a look.
Okay.
Here we go. Here we go, here we go.
I nailed that one.
I can't get out.
It was nothing.
You two idiots... Would you two idiots get up?
You guys are missing everything. The guy can't even get out of the pit.
Guys, he's asking a little girl for help!
Put your back into it!
Oh, she's abandoning him.
Guys, I'll show you how to do it better.
His pants came down.
You may be getting revenge on this, bro.
'Cause you almost killed Sal and Murr.
Clear the floor right now.
And show them the routine that you're practicing for nationals.
Uh, excuse me, everybody!
I'm gonna need everyone to clear the floor real quick.
I got to practice my routine for nationals.
And cue the music.
Oh, there's music?
There's mus-- there's music for my routine to nationals.
Nationals, what? You're a national disaster.
Ribbons! Grab the ribbons! Grab the ribbons!
This is all I got.
I'm in! I'm in!
You won me over, baby! You won me over.