Coming up, what's giving Murr an identity crisis?
Bill...the Cosby.
What?
Why is Sal acting like a bull in a liquor shop?
Olé!
And which two jokers are left hanging in tonight's big double punishment?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Today we are at Super Buy Rite Liquor Store selling spirits to customers.
As we're assisting the customers, we must do and say what the other guys tell us.
If you booze, you lose.
Wait.
If you refuse, you lose.
Give me the booze.
Give me...
Hold this. Don't...
I'll hold it.
You're really doing a bang-up job out there, Murr.
This alcohol's not gonna stock itself, guys.
You know what's funny?
I actually used to work as a stock guy.
I know. I used to work with you. You got fired.
Can I help you find anything?
Here he goes, here he goes, here he goes.
Have you ever tried this before?
No, I have not.
You're gonna love it.
All right.
Definitely try that.
Yeah, definitely.
Definitely, definitely, definitely.
Take it out of his hand, take it out of his hand.
The other one...
It's a belgian beer. It's so, so, so tasty.
I'm picking up a bunch of stuff, so why not?
You're gonna love it. It's really tasty.
Take that out of his basket, put it right back where it was.
Usually, I drink i.p.a.s.
I.p.a.s?
Yeah.
Actually, this is my this cart.
Very cool.
Have you ever had these, by the way?
Give it a try.
Murray, go get that and put it back, buddy.
Oh, you said primarily what?
I.p.a.s, mostly.
Oh, great.
He's done with you, buddy.
OK, ready, Murr?
Only speak in falsetto.
You got a party coming up?
I always have a party coming up.
Guinness, Stella.
Guinness?
I love Guinness, too. It's one of my favorites.
Nothing like going out with the boys and just pounding a Guinness, you know?
I can't tell you how many fights I've been in from pounding Guinness -- Guinni -- Guinnie.
Oh, he's walking away.
Hidey ho! See you soon!
I feel like a [bleep] idiot.
Where is Joe?
Do you need help or...
What'd you need?
Kirin.
Kirin?
Yeah.
Yeah. Bourbon's right up here.
Joe, never find it.
They'll follow you everywhere.
Right here, bud.
Oh, no, that's not it.
There you go. Uh...
Oh, that's not it, that's not it.
No. That's right. They did it over here now.
No. They put it down in the back.
Oh, here it is.
Right here.
Oh, that's not it. That's the pbr.
They're still following him.
Joe, now you follow them -- as close as you can.
The hunter becomes the hunted.
Yeah, Joe, Joe, right behind him.
They move it all around, you know?
For the holidays, it's hard to keep track, 'cause they carry so many.
We don't have it, man. I'm sorry about that.
Joe, you're being followed.
Oh [bleep] That guy's back.
The guy with the red hoodie.
He's in here every week. He asks if I'm working.
I walk into my building, he's standing there.
He's like, "well, how you been?"
I'm like, "what do you mean how have I been?"
I didn't know where I knew him from.
Pops up last week at my niece's communion.
No way.
He doesn't even drink.
He showed up at my grandmother's nursing home and tried to steal her pudding.
Joe, he's looking. Duck down behind this guy.
"If the cops need a witness, you're down, right?"
If the cops a witness that he showed up, you're down?
What?
'Cause I have a restraining order, like, pending.
He's crazy. He's absolutely crazy.
Now have the same conversation with the guy that was following you.
How's it going, buddy? You doing all right?
Find everything OK?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh [bleep] This guy's back here.
This guy's been following me.
He shows up here all the time.
And I come out of my building, and he's out front.
And he's like, "what's up?"
And I'm like, "I don't know you."
Two weeks later, I'm at my niece's communion.
He's in the church.
I'm like, "oh, you have family here?"  He's like, "no."
He showed at my grandmother's nursing home and asked for her pudding.
I got a restraining order pending, if you'd like to --
You know, if I could use you as a witness.
Yeah, yeah.
Cool. Thanks, dude. Good luck.
Guys, I'm pretty sure I'm being followed.
Sal, do the thing -- "you got something on your shirt, boop!" -- to this guy's nose.
You have, uh... boop!
Oh, my god! That's so stupid.
Sal, you see this guy over there?
Charge this guy as fast as you can.
Go!
Olé!
Sal, this guy's got a hood in the back.
Go over to him, pull his hood down, and go, "not inside."
Oh, my god.
Excuse me, sir?
Yeah?
We have the policy of the store here...
Mm-hmm.
Look, you're gonna have to -- this one here
But this, though, not inside.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, I'm sorry.
Looks great. Thank you.
Help with anything?
"You seem insecure. What's wrong?"
You seem insecure. What's wrong?
"'Cause I missed my therapist appointment today."
I missed my therapist appointment today, so...
Start listing all your problems, buddy.
I got problems, if you want to listen.
Let me start with my sister.
Every day of the week with her.
"Please come pick me up. I got to go to work."
I don't know who the dad is.
"I don't know who the dad is."
And there's my mom.
"Can I borrow money? Work is terrible."
I don't know who your father is.
"I don't know who your father is."
Don't even get me started on my grandparents.
I'm gonna find you the wine.
Need help with anything?
"Actually, I knew someone who looks like you."
I knew someone, actually, that looks like you.
A lot like you, actually.
"Yeah, you know 'Forehead Davis'"?
Do you know...
What's your name?
Jess.
Oh, OK. No, no.
We call him Forehead Davis.
OK.
"My wife looks like a pork chop."
My wife looks like a pork chop.
Anyway, I'll get you that beer.
Can I help you with anything, sir?
No.
What do you like to drink?
I'm the same way, too.
"You probably recognize me from the news."
You probably recognize me from the news.
From the news. No.
"I'm the guy that ate that dog."
I'm the guy that ate that dog.
Ate the dog.
Yeah.
"My husband looks like a pork chop."
My husband -- he looks like a pork chop.
Anyway, I'll get you that beer.
Q, grab those ping-pong balls.
You see the big guy there with the blue hat?
Oh, dude, I...
Duck behind the beer and throw a ping-pong ball over the beer and hit him.
Are you out of your mind?
Now throw six of them at him, the whole case.
Oh, don't we have fun?
All right.
Sal just did a trust fall back here.
Pop the champagne, 'cause all four jokers stayed off the loser board.
You know when you're at the butcher and you got to pull a number to be served?
That's what we're doing today with these "ain't your Mama's" tickets.
On the back of these, there are specific tasks that we must complete.
The goal it to do whatever says on the back of your ticket.
And if you can't, you're dead meat.
Butcher joke!
All right. Ja'Crispy.
What do you got?
"Put hand inside someone's shirt."
Like, Prom Night, bro.
Get your hand right in that shirt.
OK, first of all, everyone here is in a winter coat with a turtleneck and a scarf.
Sal, you're describing problems that don't matter to me, buddy.
♪ do, do, do, do
♪ I put my hand in your shirt
♪ put my hand in your shirt
♪ hey, I put my hand in your shirt
♪ I put my hand in your shirt
I love that song.
♪ put my hand in your shirt
You got to go bigger, buddy.
I mean, you got to get people's attention.
If they sing along, they might let you do it.
♪ I put my hand in your shirt
♪ put my hand in your shirt
♪ hey, I put my hand in your shirt
That arm. What's going on with that arm?
♪ put my hand in your shirt
♪ I put my hand in your shirt
You know that song?
I can't get it out of my head.
♪ I put my hand in your shirt
Your song and dance isn't working, buddy.
You need something else.
How are the wings, by the way?
Good. Good.
If you don't have hair on your chest already
Those will put hair on your chest.
That's what my grandfather said.
Here comes the way you try to make it weird and acceptable.
You got hair on your chest already or no?
Yeah.
Now what?
What are the odds I could -- I could...
What are the odds I can just feel your chest, feel what kind of hair you got there?
Not a chance.
Can I get some chickens down here?
A spectacular fail.
Which one did you get? What'd you get?
"Crawl through someone's legs."
Yeah! All right.
That's tougher than it sounds.
Well, yeah, 'cause people gonna move, right?
He's planting it.
What's your favorite kind of beef?
Rib eye.
How do you cook it, though?
Grill, grill, grill.
You want to go with...
I prefer, like, medium.
Yeah, but now what? Why are you talking to this guy? You have nothing now.
Oh [bleep] Dropped my tea.
Excuse me one second. I'll get it.
Foiled again.
Thank you.
Oh, shoot. Excuse me one second.
Let me just...right through here.
Got it. Got the tea.
All right.
I'm gonna go home and make this steak.
Thank you, my friend.
He always does it.
He always does it somehow.
How do you feel, dude? Intimidated by that thing?
A little bit, actually.
"Smell a finger."
Not your own, not your own. Not your own.
It could be any finger.
It doesn't have to be a human finger.
Who else has a finger?
Panda bears.
You guys -- you guys smell that?
Smell what?
It's a finger.
You didn't get it. You didn't get it.
Look at her face.
He got it, he got it, he got it.
It's delicious.
Here we go.
What do you got, Q?
"Completely destroy something in someone's cart."
Destroy. Q destroy.
Q smash!
Q -- wings.
This is actually pretty nerve-racking. It's super-aggressive.
Anytime the word "destroy" is in the instruction, it's hard to do.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
Santiago sent me.
Oh, let me see where he's going.
Santiago wants his money.
He told me to tell you.
And he told me -- and he told me...
He told me to send a message.
Santiago wants his money.
Santiago is not to be messed with.
Oh, my god!
Santiago is back, baby!
Sal got a ticket to ride straight to the loser board.
We're on the streets trying to collect signatures
to get a brand-new holiday officially recognized.
But we don't know the name of the holiday
because it's been creating by the other guys.
If you can't get someone to sign in support of your holiday, you lose.
Today is Smack Murr Day.
Wait. What?
It's Joe and Murr in a joker vs. joker challenge.
Hey, guys.
I'm out here collecting some signatures for a new national holiday for the mayor's office.
I wonder if you had two seconds.
The holiday is Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix Awareness Sunday.
Yeah, what is that day?
Oh, you're not familiar with Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix?
Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix Awareness Sunday is when people realize that
"Hey, Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix is going on around here."
And it's Sunday.
Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix normally falls on a Wednesday.
So now we're trying to make people realize it on a Sunday.
Because Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix Awareness Sunday
is when they're all going out in the matrix, the particle, the Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix ...
I'm out here, busting my hump, freezing my castañas off
about Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix Awareness Sunday.
When you wake up in the morning, I want you to remember five little words.
Five little words.
"I can do it...myself."
And then think of Reverse Hyperkinetic Particle Matrix Awareness Sunday, OK?
So do me a favor and sign here.
And we can get it going.
One of you needs to sign this.
They're not gonna sign.
Thank you, my friend.
No!
Thank you.
You're a good man.
You're an OK woman.
Guys.
Yeah, Murr?
I got it.
Oh, yeah, you got it.
This time, I'm gonna try to be, like, one of the people.
You don't know what it's like to be one of the people.
Give me one second.
I'm just gonna open your back panel
and I'm gonna engage human mode.
There we go.
Do a little twist there. Replace that switch. Close that back down.
His batteries were low.
I tell you what -- I need a new holiday, and so do you.
Let me tell you about it.
Ooh! There you go.
Here's the new holiday.
I'm trying to get enough signatures.
If we get enough signatures, the government will pass the holiday.
It's the... uh... Bill the Cosby.
You don't --
Hold it together, Murray.
You know Bill the Cosby, right?
"Bill...the Cosby."
Bill...the Cosby.
That was the worst Bill Cosby ever.
You've seen him on TV. He's like... Pudding Pops!
What?
Pudding -- Pudding Pops.
The -- the -- the -- the kids.
That -- was -- the worst.
Murr signed himself up for the loser board, joining Sal in tonight's double punishment.
Hey, Q, what sucks and wears skis?
Our losers today.
That's right.
And for their punishment, they're going to the top of Bear Peak.
Bear Peak!
What's at the top of Bear Peak?
Your punishment.
Your worst nightmare.
Where are you guys gonna be?
We'll be down here in the ski lodge.
I can't ski.
Well, you look like you can.
All right, stop that.
Here we go!
All right, boys.
I don't know what to do.
All right, boys, you ready?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
It's pushing me. It's pushing me. It's pushing me. It's pushing me!
I wish we always had a button that we could press that whisks them away out of our lives.
Buddy, I'm so [bleep] scared, dude.
Look at this hill.
If you fall from here, you're dead, you realize.
Don't move fast, dude.
Stop. It's, like, shaking already.
Hit the button, hit the button.
I don't like this at all. Why are we [bleep] stopped?
How's it going, guys?
This is not funny.
I don't like being suspended here, guys. It's freezing.
This is your punishment. This is it.
There we go. Look at this.
We're having a little snowball fight.
Snowball fight!
Oh, my god!
I'm nervous I'm gonna fall.
Don't make sudden movements!
Guys.
Yeah? What?
Aah! Please stop!
At this point, I'm just done with it.
I'm already done.
Oh, yeah, let's make this worse for them.
See you guys later.
Guys, it's freezing.
It's 9 degrees out here.
You guys hang out up here, all right?
Zip up. We don't want you to catch a cold.
Would you want to trade hats, by any chance?
No.
Why would I trade hats with you?
'Cause I'm cold, and you're not.
You won't just switch with me for 10 minutes?
No.
Would you switch with me?
Yeah, I would switch with you.
You would not.
Yes, I would.
You would look at me and you'd say, "that's what you get, Murr."
Yes. You [bleep] brought food.
I love it. Give me a piece.
What?
You are not giving me a piece?
I'm not giving you a piece of that. Are you nuts?
Give me my [bleep] Kitkat! [bleep]
Come on! Give me that!
Stop it! You [bleep] That's not funny!
That's what you get. What you get!
That's my only food.
Hey, guys, we felt the snowballs didn't pack the punch we wanted them to.
What I'm gonna do is shoot you with a bunch of paintballs right now.
No, you're not. That hurts.
You're very close. You're actually very close.
No! Whoa! Oh, my god!
Guys, come on!
Cut the [bleep]
I mean, this is probably the best idea we've ever had.
Its beauty is in the simplicity.
What the [bleep] man?! Stop!
Break yo self!
Break yo self, fool!