Coming up, what's got Murr hot and bothered?
Oh! So much better.
Has Sal found three new best friends?
Cheers. Ladies night.
And which joker takes the cake in tonight's big punishment?
Prepare for something amazing.
Q
Murr
Sal
Joe
Today we're hanging out at the ski lodge at the Mt. Creek Ski and Snowboard Resort.
While cruising around the lodge, we've got to do and say what the other fellas tell us.
If you refuse, you lose.
Why?!
Murr, your skin resembles a corpse that was pulled out of the river.
You're so white. What's -- what's going on?
Try to stay out of the sun you [bleep] vampire.
Murr, see the girl in the white hat?
Yeah.
So, yeah, go pull that hat down over her eyes.
Excuse me.
You guys have helmets.
Is it hard to ski with it on?
Not really.
For me, anything constricting over my head really bothers me as a skier.
The bull[bleep] has to end at one point, and the face has to get covered by a hat.
I can't have anything on me.
If I had something there, it wouldn't matter.
If I -- if I -- like, this would drive me crazy if I had that over my head.
Thank god.
But, anyways, I'm gonna go ski a black diamond.
Thank you so much.
Good work, Murr.
Well done.
Murr.
What do you got?
The girl with the white hat that you just pulled down -- pull it down again.
Did you say they were free -- the hats?
She won't even look at him.
Did you get it down over there?
Or did you get it down over there?
It was right there?
OK. Thank you so much. I appreciate it.
She literally went like this.
Hey, Murr. There's a guy passed out on the brown couch.
Lean in and just go, "sweet dreams?"
Get closer, Murray. Closer, Murray.
Do it! Do it!
Pretty sweet? Nice. Nice.
He blew it up!
Sleep tight, all right? Sleep tight, dawg.
Alright, Murr. Here's what I want you to do. I want you to go out...
Yeah.
...then come in like a bat out of hell in front of those people.
Just take off every stitch of clothes you have except for your thermals.
But do it frantically.
It is cold as [bleep] out there.
Do you guys mind if I put my stuff here for a second?
Thanks, man.
It is -- my clothes got soaked, you know?
[bleep] got real out there.
"[bleep] got real out there."
Oh! So much better.
Q, see these two ladies sitting down in front of you?
Go over and steal the woman's scarf.
Oh, my god.
He's got a scarf.
Oh, my god. The blonde doesn't even know.
That's great, Q.
Put it on.
Do a fashion show, buddy. Twirl it around.
Trying to get her attention.
Hi.
No. This is my scarf.
Are you -- are you sure this is your scarf?
'Cause I got this as a gift.
My mother-in-law made it for me.
Just -- just keep it. I hate that scarf anyway.
Thanks, honey. Have a good day.
See this Asian dude right to your right here with his arm, putting his hand up?
Yeah.
Just make it rain right over his head.
Oh, that was amazing!
Q, your cheeks look rosy red, buddy.
Yeah?
You should go warm them up by the fire.
How could you see his ass cheeks through that?
My what?!
Oh, I'm not putting my ass cheeks near the fire.
Don't tell me what you're doing. I'm telling you what you're doing.
It works this way -- we tell you.
Now that you're saying that, why don't you go warm your ass cheeks up by the fire?
Just got to warm up for a second. All right.
Take them cheeks out.
Little more.
Oh, my god!
I need a little more crack. I can't get enough crack, Q.
Oh, my god.
All right. Right?
Toasting a pair of marshmallows over here.
How about them slopes, huh, bro?
Cool.
All right. That's got thumbs up written all over it.
You idiot.
Hey, Joe. You see this girl sitting over here? She's pretty, huh?
Pigtails. Nice.
You know how some people blow kisses?
Yeah.
We want you to do the same thing, but blow farts.
Yeah, romantic farts.
You're a 37-year-old man!
Do it again! Do it again! Do it again! Do it again! Do it again!
Buddy, she's gonna walk right by you.
Do it right in her face as she passes.
This is what my life has become.
Hey, Joe.
You see the napkin dispenser in front of you?
We, uh, put a giant snowball there.
Can you pick it up, bud?
Pick it up and whale someone with it.
Pick a target, baby. Pick a target.
What do you think?
Uh, how do you start an indoor snowball fight?
Just throw it.
Snowball fight!
Take that, suckers.
What the hell?
You look like you're gonna play Alicia Keys' boyfriend in a video.
Like, what is this?
All right, Sal. You see the guy over there with the green jacket?
Yeah.
This is a no-reading zone.
So you got to stop that reading. Just close that book.
I just got to -- This is a no-reading area.
It's a no-reading area.
Close it one more time and walk away.
Sal, sit next to this group of guys here.
It's cold out there.
So cold.
It's like single digits out.
Your tongue gets numb. You got a case of numb tongue.
You guys hit the slopes?
Yeah, I've been going down all day.
I ski. I got [bleep] up out there.
Sal, the tongue's getting so numb you're hardly discernable what you're saying.
Say, "let me tell you a story," and just talk to the guy in white.
Let me tell you something.
Come out here to get, uh, a dinner.
Now perfectly legible go, "Skiing!"
Skiing!
All four jokers are safe on the slopes and safe from the loser board.
Tonight, we came for dinner at Testaccio restaurant, but we don't have a reservation.
Oh, no!
So while patrons of the restaurant are dining, we'll be joining their table as uninvited guests.
The goal is to stay for dinner without being asked to leave.
If they tell you to hit the bricks, you lose.
It's really not that bad, boys.
OK. I'm gonna go with these two girls here.
There we go. Pizza just came.
Oh, perfect timing. Perfect timing.
I'm glad we didn't have to wait that long for it.
I was telling Denise I had to get a night out, which is why I'm glad we came.
He's pretending they know each other.
I got here just in the nick of time, too, because it's freezing out there.
Freezing!
I know.
We took a cab from, like, two blocks away.
I would have done the same. I would have done the same.
Forget about it.
Now they're into chitchat. They're on small talk.
That's insane!
Now...
He's got the slice!
He took a slice?
Oh, my god.
That's their food!
The last time we were here...
Uh-huh.
....oh, god, the fried calamari is to die for.
This just goes to show how easy it is to pick up women.
This is nice. You went with the white wine.
Did you order me a glass of it?
"Did you order me?" He said.
Yeah. Absolutely.
She's playing along.
She's not.
Excuse me.
I'll have a glass of Sauvignon Blanc.
He's ordering!
Oh! Am I in her seat?
Yes.
You made it!
Hi.
You made it.
Oh, there's two of them! Now he's in a pickle.
Come on in.
They have not asked him to leave.
No. They're sitting on the bench.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Sal.
Pleasure, Joanne.
What the hell?!
The two new ones think he's part of the table.
No clue that he's not part of it.
So, how do you guys all know each other?
Her sister is married to my brother.
Oh, there you go. OK. All right.
It worked! It worked. He's in. It worked!
Can I propose a toast?
Yeah. Sure.
To friends new and old.
We don't get out enough.
No, we don't.
Let's do it more often. Cheers! Ladies night!
He's in.
Nervous?
I am nervous.
I am nervous, but...
Oh, I got this one figured out.
... I think I got this one figured out.
You have a fool-proof plan before everything we ever do.
I think I do.
Not gonna listen to it.
Who, out of everyone on this planet, do people never interrupt?
The answer, my friends, is a man of god.
He's walking around blessing people.
The sad truth of the matter is
if Murray ever stepped into a church, he would burst into flames.
Here we go.
Hello, folks. How are you, tonight?
Good. How are you?
Good. My name is minister Murray.
I'm a man of god.
He does look like a virgin.
I run the church a few blocks away.
It's, uh, Church of, uh, Saint Dalton.
Before we eat, at the restaurant, we like to say a little blessing.
They're joining hands.
Bless this food, for these, thy gifts
for those who have fortune sometimes are less fortunate than others.
Look at his face.
He's looking at Murray like we look at Murray.
Let the children's laughter remind you how you used to be.
For I believe that all who are children eventually become older.
He just said "Amen", trying to cut him off.
A few blocks away.
He's sniffing you out.
We're on the corner of, uh, Adam and, uh, Levine street.
Once they see through his bull[bleep]
they might tell him to get the hell out of here.
Like four blocks that way on the other side of the highway.
I feel, at this point, as if I'm unwelcome.
I can stay?
No!
Oh, come on! That worked?
Blessed be us all.
All right, father Murray. Well done, padre.
Q, you look good today, bud.
You do cleanup nicely.
Let me ask you something. Do I look like I have money?
It looks like you maxed out your credit card on a sports coat.
But to someone who doesn't know me, I might have money.
No. It looks like you maxed out your credit card on the sports coat.
Hi. How you guys? Enjoying the, uh -- the appetizers?
OK. Excellent. And do you mind if I, uh, join you for one quick second?
I sent over the appetizers. I just wanted to --
He sent over the appetizer.
My name's Brian Quinn.
Hi, how you doing, sir?
Good. How are you?
I am, uh, quite wealthy.I'm independently wealthy.
I have a yacht off the coast of Brooklyn.
So, I thought what I would do is come over and make an offer to you, sir...
The hell's he doing?!
...and find out how much it would be for you to, um, spend one night with me.
To him or to her?
He's taking to him.
This meal is, of course, on me.
I'll expense it as a business expense.
Who's gonna ask a guy who says, "I'll buy you dinner," to leave?
No one!
You are a genius and a cheater.
I guess we're ready to order. Are we ready to order?
Excuse me, sir. Can I get the pesto?
Cheers. Cheers.
King of the loophole. The old dirty loophole, you know.
You know what I think you got to do here?
You got to be confused and hopefully it gets infectious, right?
So if I'm confused, they probably will be.
Wait, what?
He's going right in.
Sir.
Look at this guy.
Grazie.
Nobody is saying anything.
He's got his arm on the guy's chair!
Oh, she is shooting daggers.
How does Joe even think that this is a good approach?
Oh, no. I wasn't expecting anybody.
I was -- I was happy, actually, that you guys were here
so I had someone to sit with.
Would that be all right if I joined you for dinner?
Not really? OK. Well.
I appreciate it, though.
Sorry, buddy!
Joe Gatto, party of one. It's time for your punishment.
Here we go, buddy.
Joe, take off that blindfold, you loser.
I got it. I got it. All right.
I get in this, pop out in front of -- in front of who?
Who's in there? Who's in there?
Bachelorettes!
Joe, these women are looking for some sweet moves.
They should be looking for a refund.
Get in there and bring the heat, baby. Make it happen.
Sal, am I on the floor, yet?
Joe doesn't even know where he is
'cause he's being wheeled around in a cake.
What Joe doesn't realize is that there's no bachelorette party.
He's about to jump out of a cake in front of a bunch of war veterans.
Men who have fought and won wars.
Men way better than us.
Way better than we --
Men. Men. Men.
We're boys. They're men.
Thank you very much.
Now, ladies and gentlemen, I think we need a cake.
Let's bring out the cake, boys. Where's the cake?
This is awesome.
I'm ready to go. I'm gonna -- I'm gonna own this.
Remember, these women are expecting a show, OK?
Wait till he sees what is about to happen to him!
Here we go, ladies!
Oh, god.
This is not easy to get out of.
Ta-da!
All right.
Now give a speech to these veterans thanking them for their service.
Uh, I just want to take a --
take a moment to thank everybody, uh, for their service.
I'm not a fighter.
You know, if it was up to me to defend this country
we might even be speaking German at this point or, uh...
...Korean.
Southern.
Civil war. I don't know.
I've never actually even held a gun.
I actually played "Call of Duty" once -- that video game
and I pissed myself on my couch.
I was -- I Didn't --
Where did you buy the couch, bud?
Raymour & Flanagan.
All right, Joe. Dance for the vets.
Hit it, fellas.
Oh, god.
Dance! Dance, you monkey!
Dance for the vets.
Put your heart into it. Don't shoot --
He's throwing grenades.
He's taking cover.
There's the explosion.
Oh, Joe, just stop.
Thank you.
God bless America.